{
    "Along with the United States and Canada, what country joined the North Atlantic Treaty in 1954?": {
        "original_answer": "Western Europe",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "Canada"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined the North Atlantic Treaty in 1954?"
    },
    "Along with Georgian officials, who did Ardzinba meet with on September 19, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Russian",
        "entities": [
            "Georgian officials"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Ardzinba meet with on September 19, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, where did the Palestinian uprising begin in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did the Palestinian uprising begin in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Black, who was forced out of Sony's office in April, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Arnott",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Black"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was forced out of Sony's office in April, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with American forces, what other country will hold farewell ceremonies on September 08, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Allied",
        "entities": [
            "American forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country will hold farewell ceremonies on September 08, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with the government of Tadzhikistan, what political party resigned on February 16, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "the Communist Party",
        "entities": [
            "the government of Tadzhikistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party resigned on February 16, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the French Open, what other tournament did Haarhuis win in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Wimbledon",
        "entities": [
            "the French Open"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other tournament did Haarhuis win in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Afghanistan and Pakistan, what country will Cordovez visit at June, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Iran",
        "entities": [
            "Afghanistan",
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Cordovez visit at June, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank and what other area, what area was occupied by Israel in 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other area, what area was occupied by Israel in 1982?"
    },
    "Along with Westchester County, what Connecticut county received a tornado warning on July 12, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Fairfield County",
        "entities": [
            "Westchester County"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Connecticut county received a tornado warning on July 12, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and Poland, what country was invited to join NATO in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "Poland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was invited to join NATO in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Acre, what city was hit by the October 2000 riots?": {
        "original_answer": "Jaffa",
        "entities": [
            "Acre"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was hit by the October 2000 riots?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, what other country signed a Camp David agreement in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country signed a Camp David agreement in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, Norway, the Netherlands and West Germany, what country extracted 9.5 billion barrels of oil at 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Denmark",
        "entities": [
            "Britain",
            "Norway",
            "the Netherlands",
            "West Germany"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country extracted 9.5 billion barrels of oil at 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Morgan Stanley Dean Witter, what Wall Street firm received millions of dollars in bonuses in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Lehman Brothers",
        "entities": [
            "Morgan Stanley Dean Witter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Wall Street firm received millions of dollars in bonuses in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with SBC, what company is preparing to sell video programming over their high-speed data lines in 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Verizon",
        "entities": [
            "SBC"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company is preparing to sell video programming over their high-speed data lines in 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, what Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with what other country did White Button disintegrate in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Yugoslavia",
        "entities": [
            ""
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did White Button disintegrate in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Count Basie, who did Count Basie collaborate with in 1974?": {
        "original_answer": "Frank Sinatra",
        "entities": [
            "Count Basie"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Count Basie collaborate with in 1974?"
    },
    "Along with British forces, what forces attacked 100 targets in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "British forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What forces attacked 100 targets in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Bing Crosby, who starred in the 1956 remake of High Society?": {
        "original_answer": "Grace Kelly",
        "entities": [
            "Bing Crosby"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who starred in the 1956 remake of High Society?"
    },
    "Along with Fada, Wour and Bardai, what village was bombed by Libya on September 10, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Wadi Doum",
        "entities": [
            "Fada",
            "Wour",
            "Bardai"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What village was bombed by Libya on September 10, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the United States Open, what major tournament did Tiger Woods win in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Masters",
        "entities": [
            "the United States Open"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What major tournament did Tiger Woods win in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Rudolf Wittkower, who did Donald Clarence Judd study with in the late 1950's?": {
        "original_answer": "Meyer Schapiro",
        "entities": [
            "Rudolf Wittkower"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Donald Clarence Judd study with in the late 1950's?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what other republic was Lithuania annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Baltic",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other republic was Lithuania annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Lehman Brothers, what firm received millions of dollars in bonuses in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Morgan Stanley Dean Witter",
        "entities": [
            "Lehman Brothers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What firm received millions of dollars in bonuses in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Art Blakey and Philly, who did Mr. Taylor help define the sound of jazz in the 1950's?": {
        "original_answer": "Joe Jones",
        "entities": [
            "Art Blakey",
            "Philly"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Mr. Taylor help define the sound of jazz in the 1950's?"
    },
    "Along with Britain and Denmark, what country joined the union in 1973?": {
        "original_answer": "Ireland",
        "entities": [
            "Britain",
            "Denmark"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined the union in 1973?"
    },
    "Along with Saudi Arabia, what country was angered by King Hussein's on December 09, 1990 speech?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Saudi Arabia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was angered by King Hussein's on December 09, 1990 speech?"
    },
    "Along with JAMIE MACOUN and RICK WAMSLEY, who won the Stanley Cup with the Flames in 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "RIC NATTRESS",
        "entities": [
            "JAMIE MACOUN",
            "RICK WAMSLEY"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the Stanley Cup with the Flames in 1989?"
    },
    "Along with the 31st Regiment, who served in the garrison of Boston in 1775?": {
        "original_answer": "the 29th",
        "entities": [
            "the 31st Regiment"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who served in the garrison of Boston in 1775?"
    },
    "Along with WorldCom, what company collapsed in 2002 due to accounting scandals?": {
        "original_answer": "Enron",
        "entities": [
            "WorldCom"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company collapsed in 2002 due to accounting scandals?"
    },
    "Along with Rimm, who did Dr. Duncan consult with in November, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Sirbu",
        "entities": [
            "Rimm"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Dr. Duncan consult with in November, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the Louvre, what museum authenticated the painting as a van Gogh painted in 1878?": {
        "original_answer": "Orsay Museums",
        "entities": [
            "the Louvre"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What museum authenticated the painting as a van Gogh painted in 1878?"
    },
    "Along with Al Quds, what Saudi opposition group said that six Saudi Muslim fundamentalists had confessed to carrying out the in June, 1996 bombing?": {
        "original_answer": "the Movement for Islamic Reform",
        "entities": [
            "Al Quds"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Saudi opposition group said that six Saudi Muslim fundamentalists had confessed to carrying out the in June, 1996 bombing?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country was partitioned in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was partitioned in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with Eric Cobb and Julius Erving, who was a playground star with Kirkland from 1968 to 1971?": {
        "original_answer": "Joe Hammond",
        "entities": [
            "Eric Cobb",
            "Julius Erving"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a playground star with Kirkland from 1968 to 1971?"
    },
    "Along with Gary Graffman, who suffered paralyzing injuries in 1981?": {
        "original_answer": "Leon Fleischer",
        "entities": [
            "Gary Graffman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who suffered paralyzing injuries in 1981?"
    },
    "Along with the September 11, 2004 attacks, what US ship was bombed?": {
        "original_answer": "the U.S.S. Cole",
        "entities": [
            "the September 11",
            "2004 attacks"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What US ship was bombed?"
    },
    "Along with Lorenzetti, what Siennese artist developed naturalism in the 14th century?": {
        "original_answer": "Simone Martini",
        "entities": [
            "Lorenzetti"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Siennese artist developed naturalism in the 14th century?"
    },
    "Along with Fontaine and Kauffmann, who was kidnapped in March of 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Carton",
        "entities": [
            "Fontaine",
            "Kauffmann"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was kidnapped in March of 1985?"
    },
    "Along with Angola, Guinea-Bissau, and what other country did independence wars break out in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "Mozambique",
        "entities": [
            "Angola",
            "Guinea-Bissau,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did independence wars break out in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with the Democratic National Committee, what political party received as much as $800,000 from 1992 through 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "the Democratic Party",
        "entities": [
            "the Democratic National Committee"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party received as much as $800,000 from 1992 through 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Merbah's functions, who was appointed in November, 1988 with a mandate to change Algeria into a multiparty democracy?": {
        "original_answer": "Cabinet",
        "entities": [
            "Merbah's functions"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was appointed in November, 1988 with a mandate to change Algeria into a multiparty democracy?"
    },
    "Along with Mario M. Cuomo, what actress appeared in a 1995 Doritos commercial?": {
        "original_answer": "Ann Richards",
        "entities": [
            "Mario M. Cuomo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What actress appeared in a 1995 Doritos commercial?"
    },
    "Along with Enron, what company collapsed in 2002 due to accounting scandals?": {
        "original_answer": "WorldCom",
        "entities": [
            "Enron"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company collapsed in 2002 due to accounting scandals?"
    },
    "Along with Taylor, what other bank was founded in 1692?": {
        "original_answer": "Fladgate",
        "entities": [
            "Taylor"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other bank was founded in 1692?"
    },
    "Along with the Gaza Strip, what did Israel capture in the 1967 Middle East war?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the Gaza Strip"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did Israel capture in the 1967 Middle East war?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country was invited to join NATO in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was invited to join NATO in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Hopi and Pueblo Indians, what tribe was ancestors of March 06, 1987's Hopi?": {
        "original_answer": "Zuni",
        "entities": [
            "Hopi",
            "Pueblo Indians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What tribe was ancestors of March 06, 1987's Hopi?"
    },
    "Along with Slovakia, what country split in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "The Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Slovakia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country split in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Czech Republic, what country split in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovakia",
        "entities": [
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country split in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Ewing, Jordan, Wayman Tisdale and Sam Perkins, who was on the 1984 Knight team?": {
        "original_answer": "Mullin",
        "entities": [
            "Ewing",
            "Jordan",
            "Wayman Tisdale",
            "Sam Perkins"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was on the 1984 Knight team?"
    },
    "Along with Nomura Securities Company, what bank was ordered to suspend operations for the rest of 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Dai-Ichi Kangyo Bank",
        "entities": [
            "Nomura Securities Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What bank was ordered to suspend operations for the rest of 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and the Czech Republic, what country joined NATO in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined NATO in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Angola, Mozambique, and what other country did independence wars break out in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "Guinea-Bissau",
        "entities": [
            "Angola",
            "Mozambique,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did independence wars break out in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with the Irish, what government invited parties to negotiate with them in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the Irish"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government invited parties to negotiate with them in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, what other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Motorola, what three companies were pounded after their late-on October 10, 2000 profit warnings?": {
        "original_answer": "Yahoo, Lucent",
        "entities": [
            "Motorola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What three companies were pounded after their late-on October 10, 2000 profit warnings?"
    },
    "Along with Decatur Federal Savings, what institution was investigated by the Justice Department in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Loan of Atlanta",
        "entities": [
            "Decatur Federal Savings"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What institution was investigated by the Justice Department in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Turkestan and Khorezm, what group was dismembered by Stalin in 1925?": {
        "original_answer": "the People's Republics of Bukhara",
        "entities": [
            "Turkestan",
            "Khorezm"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group was dismembered by Stalin in 1925?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what country split in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country split in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Disney and Warner Brothers, what studio dropped out on June 07, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Paramount Pictures",
        "entities": [
            "Disney",
            "Warner Brothers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What studio dropped out on June 07, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Quaker Oats, what company acquired Gatorade in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "Stokely-Van Camp Inc.",
        "entities": [
            "Quaker Oats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company acquired Gatorade in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Iran and Kuwait, what country did Izetbegovic visit in October, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Saudi Arabia",
        "entities": [
            "Iran",
            "Kuwait"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Izetbegovic visit in October, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, what Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Joe Hammond, who did Kirkland team with in 1971?": {
        "original_answer": "Eric Cobb",
        "entities": [
            "Joe Hammond"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Kirkland team with in 1971?"
    },
    "Along with Tonga and Kiribati, what other Pacific nation joined the Tuvalu organization in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Nauru",
        "entities": [
            "Tonga",
            "Kiribati"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Pacific nation joined the Tuvalu organization in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Andorra, Belgium, Luxembourg and San Marino, what other country adopted the American standard in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Liechtenstein",
        "entities": [
            "Andorra",
            "Belgium",
            "Luxembourg",
            "San Marino"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country adopted the American standard in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Ewing, Mullin, Wayman Tisdale, and Sam Perkins, who was on the 1984 Knight team?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan",
        "entities": [
            "Ewing",
            "Mullin",
            "Wayman Tisdale",
            "and Sam Perkins"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was on the 1984 Knight team?"
    },
    "Along with Chris Gatling, who did the Nets win on March 14, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Brian Evans",
        "entities": [
            "Chris Gatling"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Nets win on March 14, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with James Boswell, who was offered marmalade at breakfast in Scotland in 1773?": {
        "original_answer": "Samuel Johnson",
        "entities": [
            "James Boswell"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was offered marmalade at breakfast in Scotland in 1773?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, what other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the Beatles, what company sued EMI in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Apple",
        "entities": [
            "the Beatles"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company sued EMI in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the United States and the Commonwealth, what other country imposed sanctions on Nigeria in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "the European Union",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "the Commonwealth"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country imposed sanctions on Nigeria in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank and Israel, where did violence in 2000 keep tourists away from Egypt?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "Israel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did violence in 2000 keep tourists away from Egypt?"
    },
    "Along with Robert Starr and Jonathan Annis, who co-founded on June 26, 1994 by the Bay?": {
        "original_answer": "Don Hall",
        "entities": [
            "Robert Starr",
            "Jonathan Annis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who co-founded on June 26, 1994 by the Bay?"
    },
    "Along with Japan and Malaysia, what other country will Clinton visit on November 07, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "South Korea",
        "entities": [
            "Japan",
            "Malaysia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country will Clinton visit on November 07, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Uganda and Congo, what country signed a peace agreement in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Rwanda",
        "entities": [
            "Uganda",
            "Congo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country announced on December 19, 2004 that Libya would disclose and dismantle its weapons programs?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country announced on December 19, 2004 that Libya would disclose and dismantle its weapons programs?"
    },
    "Along with the 1990 Pontiac Grand Prix, what Chevrolet model did Polex receive orders for in its first two days of operation?": {
        "original_answer": "Corsica",
        "entities": [
            "the 1990 Pontiac Grand Prix"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Chevrolet model did Polex receive orders for in its first two days of operation?"
    },
    "Along with Sophan Sopian, who was a legislator questioned on August 13, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Sukowaluyo Mintohardjo",
        "entities": [
            "Sophan Sopian"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a legislator questioned on August 13, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the British, what armies occupied the western portion of Germany until 1955?": {
        "original_answer": "French",
        "entities": [
            "the British"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What armies occupied the western portion of Germany until 1955?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what republic was annexed by Stalin in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What republic was annexed by Stalin in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Denmark and Ireland, what country joined the European Union in 1973?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Denmark",
            "Ireland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined the European Union in 1973?"
    },
    "Along with Apple, what group sued EMI in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Beatles",
        "entities": [
            "Apple"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group sued EMI in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Muslim and Croat armies, who stopped fighting in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "the Bosnian Serb",
        "entities": [
            "Muslim",
            "Croat armies"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who stopped fighting in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the Rebel Stakes, what race did Greater Good win in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Southwest",
        "entities": [
            "the Rebel Stakes"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did Greater Good win in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what Baltic republic fell to Soviet annexation in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic fell to Soviet annexation in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Sweden and Finland, what country joined the European Union in January, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Austria",
        "entities": [
            "Sweden",
            "Finland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined the European Union in January, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the Nicobar Islands, what island was devastated by the December 26, 2004 tsunami?": {
        "original_answer": "Andaman",
        "entities": [
            "the Nicobar Islands"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What island was devastated by the December 26, 2004 tsunami?"
    },
    "Along with The World-Telegram and Sun, what newspaper did the Herald Tribune merge with in 1966?": {
        "original_answer": "The New York Journal-American",
        "entities": [
            "The World-Telegram",
            "Sun"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper did the Herald Tribune merge with in 1966?"
    },
    "Along with Rwanda and Congo, what country signed a peace agreement in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Uganda",
        "entities": [
            "Rwanda",
            "Congo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with China and Africa, what country did Paul Simon tour in 1991-92?": {
        "original_answer": "South America",
        "entities": [
            "China",
            "Africa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Paul Simon tour in 1991-92?"
    },
    "Along with Kiribati and Nauru, what other Pacific nation joined the Tuvalu organization in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Tonga",
        "entities": [
            "Kiribati",
            "Nauru"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Pacific nation joined the Tuvalu organization in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Hosni Mubarak, who did Bush meet with April, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Shamir",
        "entities": [
            "Hosni Mubarak"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Bush meet with April, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with the euro, what other currency did the American and Japanese central banks rescue on September 23, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "European",
        "entities": [
            "the euro"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other currency did the American and Japanese central banks rescue on September 23, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Italians, what occupiers did the Communists fight in June 1941?": {
        "original_answer": "German",
        "entities": [
            "Italians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What occupiers did the Communists fight in June 1941?"
    },
    "Along with Burkina Faso, what country helped Charles G. Taylor invade Liberia in 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Ivory Coast",
        "entities": [
            "Burkina Faso"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country helped Charles G. Taylor invade Liberia in 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Hilla, what Shiite area was bombed on February 03, 2007?": {
        "original_answer": "Baghdad",
        "entities": [
            "Hilla"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Shiite area was bombed on February 03, 2007?"
    },
    "Along with Jaffa, what city was hit by the October 2000 riots?": {
        "original_answer": "Acre",
        "entities": [
            "Jaffa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was hit by the October 2000 riots?"
    },
    "Along with John Hume, who won the Peace Prize in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "David Trimble",
        "entities": [
            "John Hume"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the Peace Prize in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country signed a Camp David agreement in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a Camp David agreement in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with the Republican, what political party did Kover run for State Assembly in the early 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Conservative",
        "entities": [
            "the Republican"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party did Kover run for State Assembly in the early 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, in what area did clashes continue on May 23, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza Strip",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area did clashes continue on May 23, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country joined NATO in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined NATO in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with English and Dutch, what other language came to New Jersey in the 17th century?": {
        "original_answer": "Swedish",
        "entities": [
            "English",
            "Dutch"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other language came to New Jersey in the 17th century?"
    },
    "Along with Afghan troops, who sent troops into Afghanistan in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "Soviet",
        "entities": [
            "Afghan troops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sent troops into Afghanistan in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Yitzhak Rabin, Shimon Peres and Shimon Peres, who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Yasser Arafat",
        "entities": [
            "Yitzhak Rabin",
            "Shimon Peres",
            "Shimon Peres"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Iraq, Iran, Sudan and the former Yugoslavia, what country was rebuked in similar language in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Cuba",
        "entities": [
            "Iraq",
            "Iran",
            "Sudan",
            "the former Yugoslavia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was rebuked in similar language in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with South Korea and Malaysia, what country will Clinton visit on November 07, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Japan",
        "entities": [
            "South Korea",
            "Malaysia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Clinton visit on November 07, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Scirica, who was appointed to the bench by President Ronald Reagan in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Cowen",
        "entities": [
            "Scirica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was appointed to the bench by President Ronald Reagan in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Nabila Tours, what company is adding three Nile boats in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Cruises",
        "entities": [
            "Nabila Tours"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company is adding three Nile boats in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Fluor Daniel and Motorola, what company was given a contract in 1999 to ''replace and manage'' the communications system?": {
        "original_answer": "Racal Translink",
        "entities": [
            "Fluor Daniel",
            "Motorola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company was given a contract in 1999 to ''replace and manage'' the communications system?"
    },
    "Along with moderate Hutu, what group was killed in the 1994 Rwandan massacre?": {
        "original_answer": "Tutsi",
        "entities": [
            "moderate Hutu"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group was killed in the 1994 Rwandan massacre?"
    },
    "Along with Iran, what country will Cordovez visit at June, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "Iran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Cordovez visit at June, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Norway, Denmark, the Netherlands and West Germany, what country extracted 9.5 billion barrels of oil at 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Norway",
            "Denmark",
            "the Netherlands",
            "West Germany"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country extracted 9.5 billion barrels of oil at 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Wadi Doum, Wour and Bardai, what village was bombed by Libya on September 10, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Fada",
        "entities": [
            "Wadi Doum",
            "Wour",
            "Bardai"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What village was bombed by Libya on September 10, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Italy, what country withdrew in September, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Italy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country withdrew in September, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with congressional leaders, who agreed to a deficit reduction plan on November 20, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "the White House",
        "entities": [
            "congressional leaders"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who agreed to a deficit reduction plan on November 20, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Belarus, Russia, and Byelorussia, what country signed an agreement in Minsk on December 08, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Ukraine",
        "entities": [
            "Belarus",
            "Russia",
            "and Byelorussia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement in Minsk on December 08, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Albert Museum, what London museum had four silver galleries reopened on November 27, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Victoria",
        "entities": [
            "the Albert Museum"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What London museum had four silver galleries reopened on November 27, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Hudson, Hunterdon and what other county, Gormley spent on June 04, 1989 campaigning in the north?": {
        "original_answer": "Passaic",
        "entities": [
            "Hudson",
            "Hunterdon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other county, Gormley spent on June 04, 1989 campaigning in the north?"
    },
    "Along with the center, who was indicted on April 07, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Barrie",
        "entities": [
            "the center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted on April 07, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Mrosko, who did the Giants protect on February 01, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Cross",
        "entities": [
            "Mrosko"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Giants protect on February 01, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with EADS, what other company announced that one A380 would be delivered to Singapore Airlines in October, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Airbus",
        "entities": [
            "EADS"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company announced that one A380 would be delivered to Singapore Airlines in October, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the Virgin, who did Michelangelo begin a sculpture of September 12, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Jesus",
        "entities": [
            "the Virgin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Michelangelo begin a sculpture of September 12, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country is part of the March 14, 2007 coalition?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country is part of the March 14, 2007 coalition?"
    },
    "Along with Lynn Swann, Jack Lambert and Mike Webster, who was a Steelers draft pick in 1974?": {
        "original_answer": "John Stallworth",
        "entities": [
            "Lynn Swann",
            "Jack Lambert",
            "Mike Webster"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a Steelers draft pick in 1974?"
    },
    "Along with Teheran, what city declared a cease-fire in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Baghdad",
        "entities": [
            "Teheran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city declared a cease-fire in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Kazakstan and Ukraine, what country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Belarus",
        "entities": [
            "Kazakstan",
            "Ukraine"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, Latvia, and what other country did the US refuse to acknowledge the Soviet Union's annexation of in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did the US refuse to acknowledge the Soviet Union's annexation of in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, what country did the United States clash with in 1956 over their attempt to seize the Suez Canal?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the United States clash with in 1956 over their attempt to seize the Suez Canal?"
    },
    "Along with Iraq, what country will begin a cease-fire on August 20, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Iran",
        "entities": [
            "Iraq"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will begin a cease-fire on August 20, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Gaza, where did the United Nations Emergency Force withdraw in June 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Sinai",
        "entities": [
            "Gaza"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did the United Nations Emergency Force withdraw in June 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Eastern European neighbors, what country was Bulgaria dependent on for trade until 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Soviet",
        "entities": [
            "Eastern European neighbors"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was Bulgaria dependent on for trade until 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Dublin, what two governments signed an agreement in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "London",
        "entities": [
            "Dublin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two governments signed an agreement in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with William Allen, what Philadelphia businessman leased a 3,000-acre tract from the King of England in 1742?": {
        "original_answer": "Joseph Turner",
        "entities": [
            "William Allen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Philadelphia businessman leased a 3,000-acre tract from the King of England in 1742?"
    },
    "Along with the World Trade Center, what other building was attacked by Bush in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Pentagon",
        "entities": [
            "the World Trade Center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other building was attacked by Bush in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Detroit Pistons and Syracuse Nationals, what N.B.A. team did Yardley play for from 1953 to 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "the Fort Wayne",
        "entities": [
            "the Detroit Pistons",
            "Syracuse Nationals"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What N.B.A. team did Yardley play for from 1953 to 1960?"
    },
    "Along with Norman W. Manley and Michael's father, who was the opposition leader in Jamaica in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "Alexander Bustamante",
        "entities": [
            "Norman W. Manley",
            "Michael's father"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was the opposition leader in Jamaica in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with House and Conde Nast, what magazine did she work for until 1953?": {
        "original_answer": "Garden",
        "entities": [
            "House",
            "Conde Nast"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What magazine did she work for until 1953?"
    },
    "Along with Lori L. Budo and Lori L. Budo, who was arrested on July 17, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Cheri A. Landry",
        "entities": [
            "Lori L. Budo",
            "Lori L. Budo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was arrested on July 17, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the Gaza Strip, what other area was occupied by Israel in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the Gaza Strip"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other area was occupied by Israel in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Andy Warhol, who started silk-screening photographs onto their canvases in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "Rauschenberg",
        "entities": [
            "Andy Warhol"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who started silk-screening photographs onto their canvases in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with Jordan and the Palestine Liberation Organization, what country received $3.1 billion in aid in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Syria",
        "entities": [
            "Jordan",
            "the Palestine Liberation Organization"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country received $3.1 billion in aid in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with the Nazis and the Soviet Union, what empire ruled the Czech Republic in the 20th century?": {
        "original_answer": "the Austro-Hungarian Empire",
        "entities": [
            "the Nazis",
            "the Soviet Union"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What empire ruled the Czech Republic in the 20th century?"
    },
    "Along with Ambien, what sleep aid was sold for more than $3 billion in the U.S. in 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Lunesta",
        "entities": [
            "Ambien"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What sleep aid was sold for more than $3 billion in the U.S. in 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania and Latvia, what country was annexed by the Soviets in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was annexed by the Soviets in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Satwant Singh, who was hanged in January, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Kehar Singh",
        "entities": [
            "Satwant Singh"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was hanged in January, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Hamas, what group halted attacks on June 29, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamic Jihad",
        "entities": [
            "Hamas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group halted attacks on June 29, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with shipping sources in the region, who did Reuters quote as saying Iraq hit two tankers from the air on September 01, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Lloyd's of London",
        "entities": [
            "shipping sources in the region"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Reuters quote as saying Iraq hit two tankers from the air on September 01, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Russia and Prussia, what country partitioned Poland in the late 18th century?": {
        "original_answer": "Austria",
        "entities": [
            "Russia",
            "Prussia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country partitioned Poland in the late 18th century?"
    },
    "Along with the Firenza, what J model did Cadillac and Oldsmobile drop in January, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Cimarron",
        "entities": [
            "the Firenza"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What J model did Cadillac and Oldsmobile drop in January, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Warner Brothers, who introduced the sixth and fifth broadcast networks for the 1994-95 season?": {
        "original_answer": "Paramount",
        "entities": [
            "Warner Brothers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who introduced the sixth and fifth broadcast networks for the 1994-95 season?"
    },
    "Along with Mirza Iqbal Baig, who was extradited to the United States on April 03, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Anwar Khattak",
        "entities": [
            "Mirza Iqbal Baig"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was extradited to the United States on April 03, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Nicole Brown Simpson, who was killed on June 12, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Ronald L. Goldman",
        "entities": [
            "Nicole Brown Simpson"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed on June 12, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Hungary, what country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Australia and New Zealand, what country began to dismantle its colonial empires in the 1960's and 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Australia",
            "New Zealand"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country began to dismantle its colonial empires in the 1960's and 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Glendale, what fires started on June 27, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Santa Barbara",
        "entities": [
            "Glendale"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What fires started on June 27, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Sunni, Druse and France, what political party is in the March 14, 2007 coalition?": {
        "original_answer": "Christian",
        "entities": [
            "Sunni",
            "Druse",
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party is in the March 14, 2007 coalition?"
    },
    "Along with Costa Rica, what other country objected to the choice of Los Angeles as the neutral site for July 09, 1989's World Cup qualifying game?": {
        "original_answer": "Guatemala",
        "entities": [
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country objected to the choice of Los Angeles as the neutral site for July 09, 1989's World Cup qualifying game?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, Estonia, and what other country did the Soviet Union annex in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did the Soviet Union annex in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Charles Carpenter, who did Hilbert visit on Nantucket in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Mary-Grace",
        "entities": [
            "Charles Carpenter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Hilbert visit on Nantucket in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with Philadelphia, what city did Clemens travel to in 1853-54?": {
        "original_answer": "New York",
        "entities": [
            "Philadelphia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city did Clemens travel to in 1853-54?"
    },
    "Along with Cheri A. Landry and Dr. Pou, who was arrested on July 17, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Lori L. Budo",
        "entities": [
            "Cheri A. Landry",
            "Dr. Pou"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was arrested on July 17, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Karen Stimson and what other woman did Leonard sail with in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Susan Bylander",
        "entities": [
            "Karen Stimson"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other woman did Leonard sail with in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with NATO and other European nations, what pact was formally adopted on January 16, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "the Warsaw Pact",
        "entities": [
            "NATO",
            "other European nations"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What pact was formally adopted on January 16, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Vivaldi, what Baroque composer performed at February 05, 1993's concert?": {
        "original_answer": "Thomas Arne",
        "entities": [
            "Vivaldi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baroque composer performed at February 05, 1993's concert?"
    },
    "Along with the British, what country launched air strikes in Iraq in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the British"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country launched air strikes in Iraq in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Yugoslavia and Finland, what country did Estonia and Latvia join in 1918?": {
        "original_answer": "Czechoslovakia",
        "entities": [
            "Yugoslavia",
            "Finland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Estonia and Latvia join in 1918?"
    },
    "Along with Core-states Financial Corporation, what other company did First Union buy in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Money Store Inc.",
        "entities": [
            "Core-states Financial Corporation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company did First Union buy in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Rauschenberg, who started silk-screening photographs onto their canvases in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "Andy Warhol",
        "entities": [
            "Rauschenberg"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who started silk-screening photographs onto their canvases in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with President Nixon, who bombed Cambodia in 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Henry Kissinger",
        "entities": [
            "President Nixon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who bombed Cambodia in 1975?"
    },
    "Along with MIKE BATT, who sang on a demonstration tape in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "SARAH BRIGHTMAN",
        "entities": [
            "MIKE BATT"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sang on a demonstration tape in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with South Korea, what country held talks on February 20, 1992 to defuse tensions on the nuclear issue?": {
        "original_answer": "North",
        "entities": [
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country held talks on February 20, 1992 to defuse tensions on the nuclear issue?"
    },
    "Along with Essex County, what New Jersey United Way chapter is not contributing to the Boy Scouts in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Somerset County",
        "entities": [
            "Essex County"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What New Jersey United Way chapter is not contributing to the Boy Scouts in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Jews, what group sent a telegram to Eisenhower in 1953?": {
        "original_answer": "the National Conference of Christians",
        "entities": [
            "Jews"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group sent a telegram to Eisenhower in 1953?"
    },
    "Along with the Imperials, what team did Villegas join in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Stallions",
        "entities": [
            "the Imperials"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What team did Villegas join in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Islamic Jihad, who declared a halt to attacks on June 29, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Hamas",
        "entities": [
            "Islamic Jihad"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who declared a halt to attacks on June 29, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Lunesta, what sleep aid sold more than $3 billion in the United States in 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Ambien",
        "entities": [
            "Lunesta"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What sleep aid sold more than $3 billion in the United States in 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Anthony Tennant, who was indicted in May, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Taubman",
        "entities": [
            "Anthony Tennant"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in May, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Belarus, Kazakstan and Ukraine, what country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Russia",
        "entities": [
            "Belarus",
            "Kazakstan",
            "Ukraine"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?"
    },
    "Along with Bagwell, Beltran, and Kent, who protected Biggio in the 2004 division series against the Braves?": {
        "original_answer": "Jeff Kent",
        "entities": [
            "Bagwell",
            "Beltran",
            "and Kent"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who protected Biggio in the 2004 division series against the Braves?"
    },
    "Along with the Iranians, what ethnic group did Hussein use nerve agents against in the 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Kurdish",
        "entities": [
            "the Iranians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group did Hussein use nerve agents against in the 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with Mercury, Venus, Mars, Saturn, and Moon, what planet partnered with the Moon and Sun on May 05, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Jupiter",
        "entities": [
            "Mercury",
            "Venus",
            "Mars",
            "Saturn",
            "and Moon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What planet partnered with the Moon and Sun on May 05, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Antarctica and South Georgia, where did Abbott go on a cruise in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "the Falkland Islands",
        "entities": [
            "Antarctica",
            "South Georgia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did Abbott go on a cruise in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Belarus, Kazakstan and Russia, what country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Ukraine",
        "entities": [
            "Belarus",
            "Kazakstan",
            "Russia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a modification to the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty of 1972?"
    },
    "Along with Gaza, to what area did Israel occupy in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "Gaza",
            "to"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area did Israel occupy in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Cross, who did the Giants protect on February 01, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Mrosko",
        "entities": [
            "Cross"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Giants protect on February 01, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with New York, what city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Washington",
        "entities": [
            "New York"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Allied, what other company was acquired by the Campeau Corporation in 1986 and 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Federated",
        "entities": [
            "Allied"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company was acquired by the Campeau Corporation in 1986 and 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia and Bosnia, what country seceded from Yugoslavia in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Bosnia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country seceded from Yugoslavia in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Netherlands, what country finished behind the Hockeyroos in 2000's Champions Trophy?": {
        "original_answer": "Germany",
        "entities": [
            "the Netherlands"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country finished behind the Hockeyroos in 2000's Champions Trophy?"
    },
    "Along with Serbs and Croats, what religious group fought in Bosnia in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Muslims",
        "entities": [
            "Serbs",
            "Croats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What religious group fought in Bosnia in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Muslims and Serbs, what ethnic group fought in Bosnia in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Croats",
        "entities": [
            "Muslims",
            "Serbs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group fought in Bosnia in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Cracow, Paris and Brussels, what city also signed the 1987 agreement?": {
        "original_answer": "Lyons",
        "entities": [
            "Cracow",
            "Paris",
            "Brussels"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city also signed the 1987 agreement?"
    },
    "Along with Czechoslovakia, Yugoslavia and Finland, what other country became independent in 1918?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Czechoslovakia",
            "Yugoslavia",
            "Finland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country became independent in 1918?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa, Cuba, and the United States, what country agreed that Namibia's transition to independence would begin on November 01, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Angola",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Cuba",
            "and the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country agreed that Namibia's transition to independence would begin on November 01, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what country was annexed by Stalin in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was annexed by Stalin in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Cracow, Lyons and Brussels, what city signed the 1987 agreement?": {
        "original_answer": "Paris",
        "entities": [
            "Cracow",
            "Lyons",
            "Brussels"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city signed the 1987 agreement?"
    },
    "Along with France, what country did the United States clash with in 1956 over their attempt to seize the Suez Canal?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the United States clash with in 1956 over their attempt to seize the Suez Canal?"
    },
    "Along with Karen Stimson and Susan Bylander, what boat did Leonard sail with in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Satori",
        "entities": [
            "Karen Stimson",
            "Susan Bylander"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What boat did Leonard sail with in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Angola, South Africa and what other country did Namibia have an agreement with in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Cuba",
        "entities": [
            "Angola",
            "South Africa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Namibia have an agreement with in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Michael Stewart, who was killed by police in Tompkins Square Park in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Eleanor Bumpurs",
        "entities": [
            "Michael Stewart"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed by police in Tompkins Square Park in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the Warsaw Pact, what other nation formally adopted a human rights and security agreement on January 16, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "European",
        "entities": [
            "the Warsaw Pact"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other nation formally adopted a human rights and security agreement on January 16, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Britain and Australia, what other country began to dismantle their colonial empires in the 1960's and 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "New Zealand",
        "entities": [
            "Britain",
            "Australia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country began to dismantle their colonial empires in the 1960's and 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Karbala, what Shiite holy city was bombed on February 07, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Najaf",
        "entities": [
            "Karbala"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Shiite holy city was bombed on February 07, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Carnival, what cruise line did the city sign an agreement with in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Norwegian",
        "entities": [
            "Carnival"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What cruise line did the city sign an agreement with in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Hindemith, what composer did Robert Shaw perform on January 15, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Brahms",
        "entities": [
            "Hindemith"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What composer did Robert Shaw perform on January 15, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Jubelirer and Brightbill, who lost their positions in the Republican primary on May 16, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "David J. Brightbill",
        "entities": [
            "Jubelirer",
            "Brightbill"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who lost their positions in the Republican primary on May 16, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the French, what country bombed Kuwait's embassies in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the French"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country bombed Kuwait's embassies in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Oldsmobile, what company dropped its J models in January, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Cadillac",
        "entities": [
            "Oldsmobile"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company dropped its J models in January, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the North Koreans, who fought the Chinese Communists in South Korea in 1950?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the North Koreans"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who fought the Chinese Communists in South Korea in 1950?"
    },
    "Along with Nelson Mandela, who voted to award the 2010 FIFA World Cup to South Africa?": {
        "original_answer": "Bishop Desmond Tutu",
        "entities": [
            "Nelson Mandela"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who voted to award the 2010 FIFA World Cup to South Africa?"
    },
    "Along with Iraqi forces, what country has attacked commercial vessels in the Persian Gulf since 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "Iranian",
        "entities": [
            "Iraqi forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has attacked commercial vessels in the Persian Gulf since 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Bayside Hills, what neighboring community was founded in 1935?": {
        "original_answer": "Oakland Hills",
        "entities": [
            "Bayside Hills"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What neighboring community was founded in 1935?"
    },
    "Along with Harry Vardon, who did Francis Ouimet defeat in a playoff in 1913?": {
        "original_answer": "Ted Ray",
        "entities": [
            "Harry Vardon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Francis Ouimet defeat in a playoff in 1913?"
    },
    "Along with Syria and the Palestine Liberation Organization, what Arab country received $3.1 billion in aid in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "the Palestine Liberation Organization"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country received $3.1 billion in aid in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, what other country took lands from Germany after 1945?": {
        "original_answer": "the Soviet Union",
        "entities": [
            "Poland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country took lands from Germany after 1945?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and the Czech Republic, what country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country is expected to join NATO in July, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Baghdad, what city declared a cease-fire in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Teheran",
        "entities": [
            "Baghdad"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city declared a cease-fire in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with West Haven, Waterbury and New Britain, what Connecticut city had an Eastern League team in the 1970's and 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Bristol",
        "entities": [
            "West Haven",
            "Waterbury",
            "New Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Connecticut city had an Eastern League team in the 1970's and 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with the Ivory Coast and Zaire, who will Baker meet with on November 10, 1990 in Geneva?": {
        "original_answer": "the Foreign Ministers of Ethiopia",
        "entities": [
            "the Ivory Coast",
            "Zaire"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who will Baker meet with on November 10, 1990 in Geneva?"
    },
    "Along with Satie, what composers performed at May 28, 1995's concert?": {
        "original_answer": "Vivaldi, Mozart, Britten",
        "entities": [
            "Satie"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What composers performed at May 28, 1995's concert?"
    },
    "Along with southern Shiites, what minority led the uprisings in Iraq in March, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Kurds",
        "entities": [
            "southern Shiites"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What minority led the uprisings in Iraq in March, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with France, what country left Czechoslovakia to Nazi Germany in 1938?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country left Czechoslovakia to Nazi Germany in 1938?"
    },
    "Along with Baader, Ensslin and what other prisoner died in 1977?": {
        "original_answer": "Raspe",
        "entities": [
            "Baader",
            "Ensslin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other prisoner died in 1977?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what country did Stalin seize in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Stalin seize in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with TBS and NBC, which network complained to FIFA about not being given a chance to bid for the rights to the 1994 World Cup?": {
        "original_answer": "ABC",
        "entities": [
            "TBS",
            "NBC"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which network complained to FIFA about not being given a chance to bid for the rights to the 1994 World Cup?"
    },
    "Along with Malta, what other former communist country joined the European Union in May 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Cyprus",
        "entities": [
            "Malta"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other former communist country joined the European Union in May 2004?"
    },
    "Along with the Navy, what other military branch did Danzig send officials to monitor in 1999's convention?": {
        "original_answer": "Marine Corps",
        "entities": [
            "the Navy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other military branch did Danzig send officials to monitor in 1999's convention?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country did a series of underground nuclear blasts in May, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did a series of underground nuclear blasts in May, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Mistic, Stewart's root beer and Royal Crown, what brand did Peltz and in May, 2000 want to spin off?": {
        "original_answer": "Snapple",
        "entities": [
            "Mistic",
            "Stewart's root beer",
            "Royal Crown"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What brand did Peltz and in May, 2000 want to spin off?"
    },
    "Along with Germany and Britain, what country signed an agreement with Iran in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "Germany",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with Iran in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what country declared its independence in June, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country declared its independence in June, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the Central Intelligence Agency, what agency did President Clinton read on June 24, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "the Federal Bureau of Investigation",
        "entities": [
            "the Central Intelligence Agency"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency did President Clinton read on June 24, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Sierra Club, what environmental groups sued the government in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Natural Resources Defense Council and Environmental Defense",
        "entities": [
            "the Sierra Club"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What environmental groups sued the government in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Oklahoma and West Virginia, what state had primary elections on May 10, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Nebraska",
        "entities": [
            "Oklahoma",
            "West Virginia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state had primary elections on May 10, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Beavis, what movie is scheduled for release in December, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Butthead",
        "entities": [
            "Beavis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What movie is scheduled for release in December, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the Institute of Scientific Cinematography, what organization was Franju involved with from 1938 to 1953?": {
        "original_answer": "the International Federation of Film Archives",
        "entities": [
            "the Institute of Scientific Cinematography"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization was Franju involved with from 1938 to 1953?"
    },
    "Along with Itsekiri, what ethnic group was fighting on January 31, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Urhobo",
        "entities": [
            "Itsekiri"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group was fighting on January 31, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Italy, from what country did Siad Barre gain power in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Italy",
            "from"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Siad Barre gain power in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with Xapuri, who will be sworn into office on January 01, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Acre",
        "entities": [
            "Xapuri"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who will be sworn into office on January 01, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, Jordan, Iraq and Syria, what Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?": {
        "original_answer": "Lebanon",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Jordan",
            "Iraq",
            "Syria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, what Baltic country gained independence in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country gained independence in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Czechoslovakia, what country was created in 1918?": {
        "original_answer": "Yugoslavia",
        "entities": [
            "Czechoslovakia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was created in 1918?"
    },
    "Along with the Defense Intelligence Agency, what agency missed the 1998 test evidence?": {
        "original_answer": "the Energy Department",
        "entities": [
            "the Defense Intelligence Agency"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency missed the 1998 test evidence?"
    },
    "Along with Capability Brown and Repton, who created the stately homes of present-day England?": {
        "original_answer": "William Kent",
        "entities": [
            "Capability Brown",
            "Repton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who created the stately homes of present-day England?"
    },
    "Along with Woodlawn Boys, what club did Wacquant train at 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Girls Club",
        "entities": [
            "Woodlawn Boys"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What club did Wacquant train at 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the British, what country bombed Baghdad in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the British"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country bombed Baghdad in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the US Embassies in Kenya, what country was bombed in August 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Tanzania",
        "entities": [
            "the US Embassies in Kenya"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was bombed in August 1998?"
    },
    "Along with William Kent, Capability Brown and Miles Hadfield, who created the stately homes of present-day England?": {
        "original_answer": "Repton",
        "entities": [
            "William Kent",
            "Capability Brown",
            "Miles Hadfield"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who created the stately homes of present-day England?"
    },
    "Along with the Czechs and Hungarians, what other country was admitted to NATO in March, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Poles",
        "entities": [
            "the Czechs",
            "Hungarians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was admitted to NATO in March, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the State Senate, what Democratic body voted to increase sales and income taxes in June, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Assembly",
        "entities": [
            "the State Senate"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Democratic body voted to increase sales and income taxes in June, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Sanford, what race did Kelly Kip win in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Tremont",
        "entities": [
            "the Sanford"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did Kelly Kip win in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Botswana and Mauritius, what country held multiparty elections in the early 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Senegal",
        "entities": [
            "Botswana",
            "Mauritius"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country held multiparty elections in the early 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with The Courier Journal, what newspaper did Judge Bingham buy in 1918?": {
        "original_answer": "The Times",
        "entities": [
            "The Courier Journal"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper did Judge Bingham buy in 1918?"
    },
    "Along with Hamas, what group took responsibility for August 09, 2001's terrorism?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamic Jihad",
        "entities": [
            "Hamas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group took responsibility for August 09, 2001's terrorism?"
    },
    "Along with Sabo and Smith, who reached the in October, 1993 plateaus?": {
        "original_answer": "Fernandez",
        "entities": [
            "Sabo",
            "Smith"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who reached the in October, 1993 plateaus?"
    },
    "Along with Iraq, what organization is preparing for a critical test of the agreement that averted an American military attack in February, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "United Nations",
        "entities": [
            "Iraq"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization is preparing for a critical test of the agreement that averted an American military attack in February, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Rahamim Alsheikh, what Israeli soldier was captured in Lebanon in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Yossi Fink",
        "entities": [
            "Rahamim Alsheikh"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Israeli soldier was captured in Lebanon in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Protestant paramilitaries, what group is scheduled to be disarmed on July 16, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "I.R.A.",
        "entities": [
            "Protestant paramilitaries"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group is scheduled to be disarmed on July 16, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Death Valley, what other national park was created in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Joshua Tree",
        "entities": [
            "Death Valley"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other national park was created in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Kolomon Moser, who designed a 1903 chair with a checkerboard seat?": {
        "original_answer": "Josef Hoffmann",
        "entities": [
            "Kolomon Moser"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who designed a 1903 chair with a checkerboard seat?"
    },
    "Along with East Germany, Poland and Bulgaria, what country supported the Soviets in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "East Germany",
            "Poland",
            "Bulgaria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country supported the Soviets in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Caviar King and Collins Caviar Company, what dealer introduced trout caviar in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Caviarteria",
        "entities": [
            "Caviar King",
            "Collins Caviar Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What dealer introduced trout caviar in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Paddington, what station was bombed on February 18, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Victoria Stations",
        "entities": [
            "Paddington"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What station was bombed on February 18, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Slobodan Milosevic, who slaughtered Bosnians in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Radovan Karadzic",
        "entities": [
            "Slobodan Milosevic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who slaughtered Bosnians in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Maddux, who did Schuerholz acquire in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Fred McGriff",
        "entities": [
            "Maddux"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Schuerholz acquire in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Loyalists, what political party slain many of the people in Northern Ireland between 1971 and 1977?": {
        "original_answer": "Republican",
        "entities": [
            "Loyalists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party slain many of the people in Northern Ireland between 1971 and 1977?"
    },
    "Along with Devine, who did Oppenheimer say got to the big leagues in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Hansen",
        "entities": [
            "Devine"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Oppenheimer say got to the big leagues in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, what country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Microsoft, what company had control of the PC industry in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Intel",
        "entities": [
            "Microsoft"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company had control of the PC industry in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Howard Jarvis, who initiated the tax-cutting campaign in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "Paul Gann",
        "entities": [
            "Howard Jarvis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who initiated the tax-cutting campaign in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with George Bush, who did Ross Perot defeat in the 1992 presidential election?": {
        "original_answer": "Bill Clinton",
        "entities": [
            "George Bush"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Ross Perot defeat in the 1992 presidential election?"
    },
    "Along with August, 2003 Wilson and Wynton Marsalis, who cited Bearden as an inspiration?": {
        "original_answer": "Derek Walcott",
        "entities": [
            "August",
            "2003 Wilson",
            "Wynton Marsalis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who cited Bearden as an inspiration?"
    },
    "Along with the Marshalls and the Federated States of what other country, the compact expires in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Micronesia",
        "entities": [
            "the Marshalls",
            "the Federated States of"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country, the compact expires in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Sri Lanka, what country signed a peace agreement in July, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Sri Lanka"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in July, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Joseph Cicippio and what other American was kidnapped on August 10, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Edward Austin Tracy",
        "entities": [
            "Joseph Cicippio"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other American was kidnapped on August 10, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Saudi Arabia, what other country lent money to Iraq in the 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Persian Gulf",
        "entities": [
            "Saudi Arabia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country lent money to Iraq in the 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with London, what stock exchange announced an alliance on July 08, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Frankfurt",
        "entities": [
            "London"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What stock exchange announced an alliance on July 08, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Honduras, El Salvador, Guatemala and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Nicaragua",
        "entities": [
            "Honduras",
            "El Salvador",
            "Guatemala",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the Bank for International Settlements, what bank did Leutwiler head in 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "Swiss",
        "entities": [
            "the Bank for International Settlements"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What bank did Leutwiler head in 1982?"
    },
    "Along with Israel, in what country did attacks and counterattacks on civilians cease on April 27, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Lebanon",
        "entities": [
            "Israel",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did attacks and counterattacks on civilians cease on April 27, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Fred, who gave the Southeast Asian art holdings to the museum in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Rita Richman",
        "entities": [
            "Fred"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who gave the Southeast Asian art holdings to the museum in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the World Trade Center, what other building did the on September 11, 2002 attacks attack?": {
        "original_answer": "Pentagon",
        "entities": [
            "the World Trade Center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other building did the on September 11, 2002 attacks attack?"
    },
    "Along with Nicaragua, El Salvador, Guatemala and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Honduras",
        "entities": [
            "Nicaragua",
            "El Salvador",
            "Guatemala",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Highgate Holdings, what investment fund did Wyndham sell 25 Summerfield Suite hotels to in March, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Goldman Sachs",
        "entities": [
            "Highgate Holdings"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What investment fund did Wyndham sell 25 Summerfield Suite hotels to in March, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with La Lupita, what band performed at S.O.B.'s on July 28, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Santa Sabina",
        "entities": [
            "La Lupita"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What band performed at S.O.B.'s on July 28, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Labor party, what left party was in the coalition government in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Democratic",
        "entities": [
            "the Labor party"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What left party was in the coalition government in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Angola, Cuba, what country signed an agreement with Namibia in December, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "South Africa",
        "entities": [
            "Angola",
            "Cuba"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with Namibia in December, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with A.T. Kearney and PwC, what firm laid off employees in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Booz Allen Hamilton",
        "entities": [
            "A.T. Kearney",
            "PwC"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What firm laid off employees in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Belmont Stakes, what other race did Count Fleet win in 1943?": {
        "original_answer": "Preakness",
        "entities": [
            "the Belmont Stakes"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other race did Count Fleet win in 1943?"
    },
    "Along with Oklahoma, what state was hit by a tornado on May 03, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Kansas",
        "entities": [
            "Oklahoma"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state was hit by a tornado on May 03, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what country was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the University of Chicago, what Observatory did Professor Stromgren associate with in 1936?": {
        "original_answer": "Yerkes Observatory",
        "entities": [
            "the University of Chicago"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Observatory did Professor Stromgren associate with in 1936?"
    },
    "Along with Einstein and Rosen, who attacked quantum theory in 1935?": {
        "original_answer": "Boris Podolsky",
        "entities": [
            "Einstein",
            "Rosen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who attacked quantum theory in 1935?"
    },
    "Along with Verona, what town voted to secede in November, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Cedar Grove",
        "entities": [
            "Verona"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What town voted to secede in November, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Castle Rock, what entertainment company did Ted Turner buy in August, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "New Line Cinema",
        "entities": [
            "Castle Rock"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What entertainment company did Ted Turner buy in August, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Eco, what Brazilian cable network is expected to begin broadcasting in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "CBS Telenoticias",
        "entities": [
            "Eco"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Brazilian cable network is expected to begin broadcasting in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, where has Israel occupied since 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the Gaza Strip",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where has Israel occupied since 1967?"
    },
    "Along with the Thames Conservancy, what organization did Mr. Fish work for in the 1970's and 80's?": {
        "original_answer": "Thames Water Authority",
        "entities": [
            "the Thames Conservancy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization did Mr. Fish work for in the 1970's and 80's?"
    },
    "Along with MICHAEL JORDAN, what team will the Knicks host on October 30, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "the Washington Wizards",
        "entities": [
            "MICHAEL JORDAN"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What team will the Knicks host on October 30, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Fernando Ferrer and Alan G. Hevesi, who was a mayoral hopeful in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Ruth W. Messinger",
        "entities": [
            "Fernando Ferrer",
            "Alan G. Hevesi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a mayoral hopeful in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Europe, the United States and what other country, did Gorbachev call for a summit meeting in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Canada",
        "entities": [
            "Europe",
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country, did Gorbachev call for a summit meeting in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Pickwick Papers, what Dickens story helped popularize on December 25, 1996 as a family festival?": {
        "original_answer": "December 25, 1997",
        "entities": [
            "Pickwick Papers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Dickens story helped popularize on December 25, 1996 as a family festival?"
    },
    "Along with North and Central American, what other region will the three nations represent in the 2002 World Cup finals in Japan and South Korea?": {
        "original_answer": "Caribbean",
        "entities": [
            "North",
            "Central American"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other region will the three nations represent in the 2002 World Cup finals in Japan and South Korea?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Esposito, Mrs. Zito and Mr. What other person was indicted on June 16, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Dickran",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Esposito",
            "Mrs. Zito",
            "Mr."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other person was indicted on June 16, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Westbrae Natural Foods, what other company did Vestro Natural Foods acquire in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Little Bear Organic Foods",
        "entities": [
            "Westbrae Natural Foods"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company did Vestro Natural Foods acquire in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Syria and Algeria, what country met with Qaddafi on May 28, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Tunisia",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "Algeria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country met with Qaddafi on May 28, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Hong Kong, what country signed a trade pact in June 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "China",
        "entities": [
            "Hong Kong"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a trade pact in June 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Bosnia and Herzegovina, what country was a regional power before 1350?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbia",
        "entities": [
            "Bosnia",
            "Herzegovina"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was a regional power before 1350?"
    },
    "Along with eastern Jerusalem, what area did the Israelis capture in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "eastern Jerusalem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area did the Israelis capture in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Lloyd Mangrum, who won the 1950 Open at Merion?": {
        "original_answer": "George Fazio",
        "entities": [
            "Lloyd Mangrum"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the 1950 Open at Merion?"
    },
    "Along with Honduras and Jamaica, what country will Quayle visit on January 27, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Panama",
        "entities": [
            "Honduras",
            "Jamaica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Quayle visit on January 27, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Travelers, who sold their Metrahealth joint venture to United Healthcare in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Metropolitan Life",
        "entities": [
            "Travelers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sold their Metrahealth joint venture to United Healthcare in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the State Department of Environmental Protection, what agency will begin testing six sites on April 05, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "the Federal Environmental Protection Agency",
        "entities": [
            "the State Department of Environmental Protection"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency will begin testing six sites on April 05, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Astreiko, Dranchuk, and Bronitskaya, who was convicted on August 04, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Aleksandr Shalaiko",
        "entities": [
            "Astreiko",
            "Dranchuk",
            "and Bronitskaya"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was convicted on August 04, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the World Trade Center, what other building was attacked in September, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Pentagon",
        "entities": [
            "the World Trade Center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other building was attacked in September, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Kanterbrau, what brewery did BSN acquire in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Kronenbourg",
        "entities": [
            "Kanterbrau"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What brewery did BSN acquire in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with the Golan and Sinai, what front was annexed by Israel in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the Golan",
            "Sinai"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What front was annexed by Israel in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Germany and France, what country was convulsed in antiwar demonstrations in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States",
        "entities": [
            "Germany",
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was convulsed in antiwar demonstrations in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Kosovo, what other region was stripped of its autonomy by Serbia in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Vojvodina",
        "entities": [
            "Kosovo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other region was stripped of its autonomy by Serbia in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Kentucky and Virginia, what state struck Pittston's coal mining operations on April 05, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "West Virginia",
        "entities": [
            "Kentucky",
            "Virginia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state struck Pittston's coal mining operations on April 05, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Ice Cube, who starred in ''on July 24, 1998''?": {
        "original_answer": "Chris Tucker",
        "entities": [
            "Ice Cube"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who starred in ''on July 24, 1998''?"
    },
    "Along with the House, what other chamber passed a catchall spending bill in December, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other chamber passed a catchall spending bill in December, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Islamabad, in what city did violence flare on February 13, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Lahore",
        "entities": [
            "Islamabad",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city did violence flare on February 13, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the Florida Derby, what other race did he win in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the Wood Memorial",
        "entities": [
            "the Florida Derby"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other race did he win in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Nicaragua, Honduras, Guatemala and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "El Salvador",
        "entities": [
            "Nicaragua",
            "Honduras",
            "Guatemala",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with West Germany, who said they expected a final agreement on German unification to be concluded in Moscow on September 12, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "The Soviet Union",
        "entities": [
            "West Germany"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who said they expected a final agreement on German unification to be concluded in Moscow on September 12, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Marriott and Envergure of France, what hotel has signed deals to build 2,000 rooms by 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Holiday Inn",
        "entities": [
            "Marriott",
            "Envergure of France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What hotel has signed deals to build 2,000 rooms by 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Kia and Deanthony Walker, what baby was found dead in their cribs on January 13, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Mia",
        "entities": [
            "Kia",
            "Deanthony Walker"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What baby was found dead in their cribs on January 13, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with the U.A.W., what other union signed contracts with G.M. in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Canadian Auto Workers",
        "entities": [
            "the U.A.W."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other union signed contracts with G.M. in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Lennon, who did Lukas see get out of a limousine in 1965?": {
        "original_answer": "Paul McCartney",
        "entities": [
            "Lennon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Lukas see get out of a limousine in 1965?"
    },
    "Along with Kosovo, what other country did NATO strike on January 17, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbia",
        "entities": [
            "Kosovo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did NATO strike on January 17, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Marius Petipa, who did Sergeyev cut the entire mime of the 1895 ''Swan Lake''?": {
        "original_answer": "Lev Ivanov",
        "entities": [
            "Marius Petipa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Sergeyev cut the entire mime of the 1895 ''Swan Lake''?"
    },
    "Along with Samarra, what city was bombed on January 27, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Baquba",
        "entities": [
            "Samarra"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was bombed on January 27, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Miklos Gimes, what general was hanged on June 16, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Maleter",
        "entities": [
            "Miklos Gimes"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What general was hanged on June 16, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Serbian and federal army units, what country's national guard fought for a October 06, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Serbian",
            "federal army units"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country's national guard fought for a October 06, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Garson Kanin, what theatrical luminary corrupted Anne's diary for Broadway consumption in 1955?": {
        "original_answer": "Lillian Hellman",
        "entities": [
            "Garson Kanin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What theatrical luminary corrupted Anne's diary for Broadway consumption in 1955?"
    },
    "Along with Cybercorp, what company did Schwab acquire in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "U.S. Trust",
        "entities": [
            "Cybercorp"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Schwab acquire in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Nakhichevansky, what region was under Azerbaijani control in 1924?": {
        "original_answer": "Nagorno-Karabakh",
        "entities": [
            "Nakhichevansky"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What region was under Azerbaijani control in 1924?"
    },
    "Along with Communists, who formed a Popular Front government in Paris in 1936?": {
        "original_answer": "Socialists",
        "entities": [
            "Communists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who formed a Popular Front government in Paris in 1936?"
    },
    "Along with the former Communists, what opposition group said they would abstain from voting in May 08, 1993's confidence vote?": {
        "original_answer": "the Northern League",
        "entities": [
            "the former Communists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What opposition group said they would abstain from voting in May 08, 1993's confidence vote?"
    },
    "Along with American experts, what country said thousands of antelope dropped dead on the plateau in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Uzbek",
        "entities": [
            "American experts"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country said thousands of antelope dropped dead on the plateau in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Motorola, what company joined with Apple in 1991 to develop the Power PC?": {
        "original_answer": "I.B.M.",
        "entities": [
            "Motorola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company joined with Apple in 1991 to develop the Power PC?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country fought over the region in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "China",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country fought over the region in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, what country believed they could use the Security Council to thwart Genscher's pledge to recognize Croatia and Slovenia by December 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country believed they could use the Security Council to thwart Genscher's pledge to recognize Croatia and Slovenia by December 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country has provided military support to the Chadian government since 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has provided military support to the Chadian government since 1983?"
    },
    "Along with the Vietnamese, what country has invaded Cambodia since the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the Vietnamese"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has invaded Cambodia since the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Congress, what did Fujimori disband in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the Supreme Court",
        "entities": [
            "Congress"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did Fujimori disband in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Omarska and Manjaca, what concentration camp received attention from a horrified world in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Turnpolje",
        "entities": [
            "Omarska",
            "Manjaca"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What concentration camp received attention from a horrified world in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Charles Carroll, who was elected to the United States Senate in 1789?": {
        "original_answer": "John Henry",
        "entities": [
            "Charles Carroll"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was elected to the United States Senate in 1789?"
    },
    "Along with Ping An Insurance, what insurance company went public in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "China Life Insurance",
        "entities": [
            "Ping An Insurance"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What insurance company went public in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Jordan, what Arab state participated in a peace conference in Madrid in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Jordan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab state participated in a peace conference in Madrid in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Albert Einstein and Boris Podolsky, who attacked quantum theory in 1935?": {
        "original_answer": "Nathan Rosen",
        "entities": [
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Boris Podolsky"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who attacked quantum theory in 1935?"
    },
    "Along with Irving and Irving, who wrote a 1962 text extolling the smothering-mother theory of homosexual illness?": {
        "original_answer": "Toby Bieber",
        "entities": [
            "Irving",
            "Irving"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who wrote a 1962 text extolling the smothering-mother theory of homosexual illness?"
    },
    "Along with Lockheed and what other company did Litton Industries announce a $10 billion deal on August 30, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "the Martin Marietta Corporation",
        "entities": [
            "Lockheed"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company did Litton Industries announce a $10 billion deal on August 30, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country sent troops to Kashmir in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country sent troops to Kashmir in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with the Slovenes, what ethnic group believes that Milosevic is ready to talk about rewriting the 1974 constitution?": {
        "original_answer": "Croats",
        "entities": [
            "the Slovenes"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group believes that Milosevic is ready to talk about rewriting the 1974 constitution?"
    },
    "Along with HBM/ Creamer and Travisano & Partners, what other company did WCRS Group of London acquire in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Della Femina",
        "entities": [
            "HBM/ Creamer",
            "Travisano & Partners"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company did WCRS Group of London acquire in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Affirmated, Seattle Slew and Spectacular Bid, who was a juvenile champion in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Secretariat",
        "entities": [
            "Affirmated",
            "Seattle Slew",
            "Spectacular Bid"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a juvenile champion in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the San Fernando, what race did Flying Continental win in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Strub",
        "entities": [
            "the San Fernando"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did Flying Continental win in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Szczecin and Gdansk, what Baltic port city was shot by troops in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Gdynia",
        "entities": [
            "Szczecin",
            "Gdansk"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic port city was shot by troops in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with Ford Motor and John Deere, what company did Rogers sell in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Scott Paper",
        "entities": [
            "Ford Motor",
            "John Deere"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Rogers sell in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Manger Square, what church was not invaded in March, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "the Church of the Nativity",
        "entities": [
            "Manger Square"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What church was not invaded in March, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the United States and France, what country created a zone in northern Iraq in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country created a zone in northern Iraq in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Weinstein Company, what broadcaster made a press release in October, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "BBC",
        "entities": [
            "the Weinstein Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What broadcaster made a press release in October, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Gloria Karlson, who will teach workshops at the center in May, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Frankel",
        "entities": [
            "Gloria Karlson"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who will teach workshops at the center in May, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Cozumel, what city was evacuated on October 20, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Cancun",
        "entities": [
            "Cozumel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was evacuated on October 20, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Alen Boksic, who did Croatia struggle to replace in the 2002 World Cup?": {
        "original_answer": "Davor Suker",
        "entities": [
            "Alen Boksic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Croatia struggle to replace in the 2002 World Cup?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what country was annexed by the Soviets in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was annexed by the Soviets in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with St. Croix and St. John, what Caribbean island was purchased from Denmark in 1917?": {
        "original_answer": "St. Thomas",
        "entities": [
            "St. Croix",
            "St. John"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Caribbean island was purchased from Denmark in 1917?"
    },
    "Along with Cutter & Company, what two brokerage firms were named in the arbitration complaint filed in January, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Consolidated and against",
        "entities": [
            "Cutter & Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two brokerage firms were named in the arbitration complaint filed in January, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Georgia, Moldavia, Latvia, Lithuania and Estonia, what country refused to sign the in April, 1991 agreement?": {
        "original_answer": "Armenia",
        "entities": [
            "Georgia",
            "Moldavia",
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country refused to sign the in April, 1991 agreement?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviet Union, what country said they expected a final agreement on German unification to be concluded in Moscow on September 12, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "West Germany",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviet Union"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country said they expected a final agreement on German unification to be concluded in Moscow on September 12, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Leslie Caron, who was a ballerina for Mr. Petit in the 1940's?": {
        "original_answer": "Violette Verdy",
        "entities": [
            "Leslie Caron"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a ballerina for Mr. Petit in the 1940's?"
    },
    "Along with the White House Chief of Staff, Secretary of what branch of government did Baker serve from 1981 to 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Treasury",
        "entities": [
            "the White House Chief of Staff",
            "Secretary of"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What branch of government did Baker serve from 1981 to 1993?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country split the subcontinent in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country split the subcontinent in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with Loewe, who did Harris tour with for 20-25 weeks a year from 1982 to 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Lerner",
        "entities": [
            "Loewe"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Harris tour with for 20-25 weeks a year from 1982 to 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Didier Ratsiraka, who was elected president in December, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Marc Ravalomanana",
        "entities": [
            "Didier Ratsiraka"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was elected president in December, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Baader and Raspe, who died in the Stammheim prison fortress in 1977?": {
        "original_answer": "Ensslin",
        "entities": [
            "Baader",
            "Raspe"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who died in the Stammheim prison fortress in 1977?"
    },
    "Along with El Salvador, what country did Mitch traverse on November 08, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Guatemala",
        "entities": [
            "El Salvador"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Mitch traverse on November 08, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Tripoli and Beirut, what port was bombed on July 15, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Jbeil",
        "entities": [
            "Tripoli",
            "Beirut"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What port was bombed on July 15, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt and Syria, what country boycotted Jordan in 1958?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraq",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Syria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country boycotted Jordan in 1958?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what Baltic republic was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Arafat and Rabin, who received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Peres",
        "entities": [
            "Arafat",
            "Rabin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, what country signed the Joint Declaration in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "China",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed the Joint Declaration in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Congress, who created a commission to investigate the on September 11, 2003 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "the White House",
        "entities": [
            "Congress"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who created a commission to investigate the on September 11, 2003 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with China, what other country did not join as nuclear nations until 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "China"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did not join as nuclear nations until 1992?"
    },
    "Along with August, 2003 Wilson, Derek Walcott and others, who cited Bearden as an inspiration?": {
        "original_answer": "Wynton Marsalis",
        "entities": [
            "August",
            "2003 Wilson",
            "Derek Walcott",
            "others"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who cited Bearden as an inspiration?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa, Angola and the United States, what country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Cuba",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Angola",
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Washington Heights, what city has Farrell represented since 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Harlem",
        "entities": [
            "Washington Heights"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city has Farrell represented since 1975?"
    },
    "Along with Ghana and Hungary, what country will host a tournament in April, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Jamaica",
        "entities": [
            "Ghana",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will host a tournament in April, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the White House, what party has been investigating campaign finance abuses in the 1996 election?": {
        "original_answer": "Democrats",
        "entities": [
            "the White House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What party has been investigating campaign finance abuses in the 1996 election?"
    },
    "Along with Robert A. M. Stern, what architect modernized Hackett's home in 1976?": {
        "original_answer": "John S. Hagmann",
        "entities": [
            "Robert A. M. Stern"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What architect modernized Hackett's home in 1976?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country sent troops to Kashmir in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country sent troops to Kashmir in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with Sega, what company released high-quality 32-bit gaming consoles on June 03, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Sony",
        "entities": [
            "Sega"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company released high-quality 32-bit gaming consoles on June 03, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Nazis, what group rioted in Berlin in 1933?": {
        "original_answer": "Communists",
        "entities": [
            "Nazis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group rioted in Berlin in 1933?"
    },
    "Along with the Patriotic Union of Kurdistan, what political party ruled Iraq in May, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the Kurdish Democratic party",
        "entities": [
            "the Patriotic Union of Kurdistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party ruled Iraq in May, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Bensad, who was arrested in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Belkacem",
        "entities": [
            "Bensad"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was arrested in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what republic declared independence in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What republic declared independence in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with England, what other country was merged into the United Kingdom in 1536?": {
        "original_answer": "Wales",
        "entities": [
            "England"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was merged into the United Kingdom in 1536?"
    },
    "Along with Stanislavsky, what musical theater did he direct in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Nemirovich-Danchenko Musical Theater",
        "entities": [
            "Stanislavsky"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What musical theater did he direct in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Montana and Rhode Island, what state debated bills that would allow same-sex marriage in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Connecticut",
        "entities": [
            "Montana",
            "Rhode Island"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state debated bills that would allow same-sex marriage in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with the US, what country did the Mahdi Army fight in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraqi",
        "entities": [
            "the US"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the Mahdi Army fight in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Qatar, what other country did the two men visit on January 08, 1988 to push their mediation effort with Iran?": {
        "original_answer": "Oman",
        "entities": [
            "Qatar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did the two men visit on January 08, 1988 to push their mediation effort with Iran?"
    },
    "Along with Niger's Tuareg, what tribesmen revolted in the 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Hausa",
        "entities": [
            "Niger's Tuareg"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What tribesmen revolted in the 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with the Ranger and New Jersey, what carrier patrolled the sea around South Korea during the Asian Games in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Vinson",
        "entities": [
            "the Ranger",
            "New Jersey"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What carrier patrolled the sea around South Korea during the Asian Games in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with the Senate, to what body will Kean deliver a speech on January 13, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Assembly",
        "entities": [
            "the Senate",
            "to"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What body will Kean deliver a speech on January 13, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Virgin Records, what band has Starbucks made a deal with to sell rare tracks from 1971-2003?": {
        "original_answer": "the Rolling Stones",
        "entities": [
            "Virgin Records"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What band has Starbucks made a deal with to sell rare tracks from 1971-2003?"
    },
    "Along with Tennessee and Kentucky, what state was hit by tornadoes on April 17, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Arkansas",
        "entities": [
            "Tennessee",
            "Kentucky"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state was hit by tornadoes on April 17, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what country seceded from the Yugoslav federation in June 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country seceded from the Yugoslav federation in June 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, what country will Russian troops be out of on August 31, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Russian troops be out of on August 31, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with 45th Street, on what street did row house construction flourish west of Fifth Avenue in the 1850's and 1860's?": {
        "original_answer": "42nd",
        "entities": [
            "45th Street",
            "on"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What street did row house construction flourish west of Fifth Avenue in the 1850's and 1860's?"
    },
    "Along with Summit, what Hartford hotel closed in 1990 due to lack of business?": {
        "original_answer": "Parkview Hilton",
        "entities": [
            "Summit"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Hartford hotel closed in 1990 due to lack of business?"
    },
    "Along with William Kent and Repton, who created the stately homes of present-day England?": {
        "original_answer": "Capability Brown",
        "entities": [
            "William Kent",
            "Repton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who created the stately homes of present-day England?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what organization poured millions of dollars into stabilizing Somalia in the 1990s?": {
        "original_answer": "the United Nations",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization poured millions of dollars into stabilizing Somalia in the 1990s?"
    },
    "Along with the United Nations refugee agency, what country was criticized for the Sudanese attack on December 30, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "the United Nations refugee agency"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was criticized for the Sudanese attack on December 30, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country did Powell visit on July 29, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Powell visit on July 29, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the Czech Republic and Hungary, what other former Warsaw Pact member was admitted to NATO in July 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "the Czech Republic",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other former Warsaw Pact member was admitted to NATO in July 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Steve Biko, who did Sampson keep in touch with after the A.N.C was banned in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "Walter Sisulu",
        "entities": [
            "Steve Biko"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Sampson keep in touch with after the A.N.C was banned in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with Bryan Adams, R.E.M., Bonnie Raitt and Natalie Cole, who was nominated for record of 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Amy Grant",
        "entities": [
            "Bryan Adams",
            "R.E.M.",
            "Bonnie Raitt",
            "Natalie Cole"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was nominated for record of 1992?"
    },
    "Along with St. Thomas and St. John, what Caribbean island was purchased from Denmark in 1917?": {
        "original_answer": "St. Croix",
        "entities": [
            "St. Thomas",
            "St. John"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Caribbean island was purchased from Denmark in 1917?"
    },
    "Along with Credit Suisse, what bank did Swissair announce a deal with on October 01, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "UBS",
        "entities": [
            "Credit Suisse"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What bank did Swissair announce a deal with on October 01, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Ford, Mercury and Jaguar, what division of Ford sold 406,991 cars and light trucks in June, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Lincoln",
        "entities": [
            "Ford",
            "Mercury",
            "Jaguar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What division of Ford sold 406,991 cars and light trucks in June, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with India, what other country claimed the Kashmir region in 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country claimed the Kashmir region in 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Bosnian Muslims, what other ethnic group was indicted in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Croat",
        "entities": [
            "Bosnian Muslims"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other ethnic group was indicted in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the South African Indian Congress, what political group did Malan lead in 1952?": {
        "original_answer": "the African National Congress",
        "entities": [
            "the South African Indian Congress"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political group did Malan lead in 1952?"
    },
    "Along with Bada Shanren, what 17th-century painting did Mr. Chen fake?": {
        "original_answer": "Daoji",
        "entities": [
            "Bada Shanren"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What 17th-century painting did Mr. Chen fake?"
    },
    "Along with James B. Moseley, who reopened Suffolk Downs in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "John Hall",
        "entities": [
            "James B. Moseley"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who reopened Suffolk Downs in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what other lands did Israel occupy in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza Strip",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other lands did Israel occupy in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what country did Bonn say it will recognize by December 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Bonn say it will recognize by December 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Eduardo Costa and Hannah Weiner, who organized a wild fashion show in 1969?": {
        "original_answer": "John Perrault",
        "entities": [
            "Eduardo Costa",
            "Hannah Weiner"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who organized a wild fashion show in 1969?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country did Powell visit on July 29, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Powell visit on July 29, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the F.B.I., what agency may have bungled opportunities to thwart the on September 11, 2004 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "C.I.A.",
        "entities": [
            "the F.B.I."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency may have bungled opportunities to thwart the on September 11, 2004 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with Loch Lomond, what other national park was named in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Trossachs",
        "entities": [
            "Loch Lomond"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other national park was named in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the National Liberation Front, what opposition group won Algeria's independence in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "the Front of Socialist Forces",
        "entities": [
            "the National Liberation Front"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What opposition group won Algeria's independence in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country conducted underground nuclear blasts in May, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country conducted underground nuclear blasts in May, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa, Angola, Cuba and what other country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "the Uited States",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Angola",
            "Cuba"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other country did Quayle reopen embassies that had been closed since the 1940's?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Quayle reopen embassies that had been closed since the 1940's?"
    },
    "Along with Lorenzo Crawford and Lorenzo Crawford, who was acquitted of rape in March of 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Justin Smith",
        "entities": [
            "Lorenzo Crawford",
            "Lorenzo Crawford"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was acquitted of rape in March of 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Senator Dukakis, who co-authored the Jobs Training And Partnership Act of 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "Edward M. Kennedy",
        "entities": [
            "Senator Dukakis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who co-authored the Jobs Training And Partnership Act of 1982?"
    },
    "Along with Bohemia, Moravia and what other country did Jews migrate from between 1860 and 1910?": {
        "original_answer": "Galicia",
        "entities": [
            "Bohemia",
            "Moravia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Jews migrate from between 1860 and 1910?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, the Czech Republic and Romania, what country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic",
            "Romania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with the Voyager 2, which missions collected information on the Jovian system in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "the Voyager 1",
        "entities": [
            "the Voyager 2"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which missions collected information on the Jovian system in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with the United Nations, what other country has officials said that the men who surrendered on October 07, 1997 could offer evidence against senior Croatian political leaders?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the United Nations"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country has officials said that the men who surrendered on October 07, 1997 could offer evidence against senior Croatian political leaders?"
    },
    "Along with Arafat, who was expelled from Damascus in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "Abu Jihad",
        "entities": [
            "Arafat"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was expelled from Damascus in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Westhampton Beach, what Long Island beach cracked the Top 20 in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "East Hampton Beach",
        "entities": [
            "Westhampton Beach"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Long Island beach cracked the Top 20 in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Hume's Social Democratic, what other party defeated Sinn Fein in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Labor Party",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Hume's Social Democratic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other party defeated Sinn Fein in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania and Estonia, what small independent nation did Moscow control in 1939 and 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What small independent nation did Moscow control in 1939 and 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, Latvia and Byelorussia, what Baltic republic was admitted to the General Assembly in September, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia",
            "Byelorussia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was admitted to the General Assembly in September, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Zaire, in what country have the United Nations agencies canceled all employees' leave until January, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Rwanda",
        "entities": [
            "Zaire",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country have the United Nations agencies canceled all employees' leave until January, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the pacifist, what other faction clashed violently in 1944?": {
        "original_answer": "anti-Nazi",
        "entities": [
            "the pacifist"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other faction clashed violently in 1944?"
    },
    "Along with Mazar-i-Sharif, what city was captured by the Taliban in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Bamiyan",
        "entities": [
            "Mazar-i-Sharif"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was captured by the Taliban in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the Federated States of Micronesia, what two countries agreed to a compact of free association with the United States in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "The Marshall Islands",
        "entities": [
            "the Federated States of Micronesia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two countries agreed to a compact of free association with the United States in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with the Politburo, what committee resigns on December 03, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Central Committee",
        "entities": [
            "the Politburo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What committee resigns on December 03, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, what country does Baker visit on November 06, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country does Baker visit on November 06, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Brussels and Flanders, what region was Belgium a federation of in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Wallonia",
        "entities": [
            "Brussels",
            "Flanders"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What region was Belgium a federation of in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with George Zachary, what other venture capitalist was a rare species in Silicon Valley in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "David Sze",
        "entities": [
            "George Zachary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other venture capitalist was a rare species in Silicon Valley in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Swapo, what other country was a party to the 1978 Namibian independence plan?": {
        "original_answer": "South Africa",
        "entities": [
            "Swapo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was a party to the 1978 Namibian independence plan?"
    },
    "Along with Pol Pot, who did Khieu Ponnary defect to in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Khmer Rouge",
        "entities": [
            "Pol Pot"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Khieu Ponnary defect to in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Orion, who expressed hopes that Orion could be licensed for passenger service by April 01, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Eastern",
        "entities": [
            "Orion"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who expressed hopes that Orion could be licensed for passenger service by April 01, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the National Labor Relations Act of 1935, what program did Roosevelt support?": {
        "original_answer": "Social Security",
        "entities": [
            "the National Labor Relations Act of 1935"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What program did Roosevelt support?"
    },
    "Along with Vioxx, what prescription pain reliever exploded onto the scene in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Celebrex",
        "entities": [
            "Vioxx"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What prescription pain reliever exploded onto the scene in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country abruptly called the conference for January, 1990 l991?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country abruptly called the conference for January, 1990 l991?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviet Union, what country annexed German lands after 1945?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviet Union"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country annexed German lands after 1945?"
    },
    "Along with Azerbaijan, in what country were nearly 100 people killed in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Armenia",
        "entities": [
            "Azerbaijan",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country were nearly 100 people killed in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Bolu, what city was devastated by the August, 1999 quake?": {
        "original_answer": "Duzce",
        "entities": [
            "Bolu"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was devastated by the August, 1999 quake?"
    },
    "Along with Persia and Britain, what country contested the mountains of Central Asia in the early 1800's?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "Persia",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country contested the mountains of Central Asia in the early 1800's?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country has insisted that North Korea enter negotiations to replace the fragile armistice that ended the Korean War in 1953?": {
        "original_answer": "South Korea",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has insisted that North Korea enter negotiations to replace the fragile armistice that ended the Korean War in 1953?"
    },
    "Along with Izrael and Traznea, what Jewish family was killed by Hungarian troops in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Weiss",
        "entities": [
            "Izrael",
            "Traznea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Jewish family was killed by Hungarian troops in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, Syria, and Iraq, what other Arab nation had broken relations with the United States in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Syria",
            "and Iraq"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Arab nation had broken relations with the United States in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with a Belgian, what other national was killed in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Australian",
        "entities": [
            "a Belgian"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other national was killed in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what city did the Israelis capture in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Jerusalem",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city did the Israelis capture in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, Golan Heights, East Jerusalem, and East Jerusalem, what other area did Israel conquer in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "Golan Heights",
            "East Jerusalem",
            "and East Jerusalem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other area did Israel conquer in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Roseland, what two towns voted for secession in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Montclair",
        "entities": [
            "Roseland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two towns voted for secession in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Arabs, what other group took the floor in Libya's defense on April 01, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamic",
        "entities": [
            "Arabs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other group took the floor in Libya's defense on April 01, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Fayez Ahmed, who was on United Airlines Flight 175, scheduled for Sept. 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Mohand M. Alshehri",
        "entities": [
            "Fayez Ahmed"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was on United Airlines Flight 175, scheduled for Sept. 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, Hungary, and Russia, what country joined NATO in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary",
            "and Russia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined NATO in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Petite Sophisticate and in August, 2001 Max Woman, what clothing chain does Del Vecchio run?": {
        "original_answer": "Casual Corner",
        "entities": [
            "Petite Sophisticate",
            "in August",
            "2001 Max Woman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What clothing chain does Del Vecchio run?"
    },
    "Along with On Divorce, what book did Stein add to her children's books in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "The Adopted One''",
        "entities": [
            "On Divorce"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What book did Stein add to her children's books in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Bill Clinton, who was a presidential call-in candidate in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Ross Perot",
        "entities": [
            "Bill Clinton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a presidential call-in candidate in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Nino Cerruti, Kenzo, and Claude Montana, who is seen on March 15, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Karl Lagerfeld",
        "entities": [
            "Nino Cerruti",
            "Kenzo",
            "and Claude Montana"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who is seen on March 15, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Ross Perot, who was a presidential candidate in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Bill Clinton",
        "entities": [
            "Ross Perot"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a presidential candidate in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Powell, what other US officer was sentenced to life in prison in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Officers Koon",
        "entities": [
            "Powell"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other US officer was sentenced to life in prison in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the British, what other country occupied Gibraltar in 1704?": {
        "original_answer": "Dutch",
        "entities": [
            "the British"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country occupied Gibraltar in 1704?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what other republic declared its independence in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other republic declared its independence in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviet Union, Poland, East Germany, and Bulgaria, what country invaded Czechoslovakia in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviet Union",
            "Poland",
            "East Germany",
            "and Bulgaria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country invaded Czechoslovakia in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with the International Monetary Fund, who did Kaunda break relations with in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "the World Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the International Monetary Fund"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Kaunda break relations with in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the Senate Democrats, what party agreed that a referendum on Puerto Rico's future would be delayed until 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Republicans",
        "entities": [
            "the Senate Democrats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What party agreed that a referendum on Puerto Rico's future would be delayed until 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Glauber, who directed Brady's study of the stock market crash of 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Mullins",
        "entities": [
            "Glauber"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who directed Brady's study of the stock market crash of 1987?"
    },
    "Along with France and Belgium, which European Community member accepted the American position at the Security Council on May 29, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "France",
            "Belgium"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which European Community member accepted the American position at the Security Council on May 29, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Bohemia and what other country did Hitler occupy in 1939?": {
        "original_answer": "Moravia",
        "entities": [
            "Bohemia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Hitler occupy in 1939?"
    },
    "Along with South Korea, what country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Japan",
        "entities": [
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with the Christian Admiral, what historic building came in a package in the 1995 bankruptcy?": {
        "original_answer": "Congress Hall",
        "entities": [
            "the Christian Admiral"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What historic building came in a package in the 1995 bankruptcy?"
    },
    "Along with the A.C.C., what other conference brought in more than $16 million in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "the Big East",
        "entities": [
            "the A.C.C."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other conference brought in more than $16 million in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa, Cuba and what country signed a protocol in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Angola",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Cuba"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a protocol in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Christians, what religious group fought in Plateau in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Muslims",
        "entities": [
            "Christians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What religious group fought in Plateau in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Zidane, Batigol and Maldini, who looked like they were running in quicksand in June, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Figo",
        "entities": [
            "Zidane",
            "Batigol",
            "Maldini"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who looked like they were running in quicksand in June, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa and Cuba, what country signed an agreement with the United Nations on December 22, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Angola",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Cuba"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with the United Nations on December 22, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with The Times, what newspaper did Grigg write for after The Guardian closed in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "The Spectator",
        "entities": [
            "The Times"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper did Grigg write for after The Guardian closed in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with the Rwandan Army, what group was responsible for the 1994 massacre of hundreds of thousands of Tutsi?": {
        "original_answer": "Hutu militias",
        "entities": [
            "the Rwandan Army"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group was responsible for the 1994 massacre of hundreds of thousands of Tutsi?"
    },
    "Along with Italy, what country left the European monetary system in September, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "Italy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country left the European monetary system in September, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Saudi Arabia, Pakistan, Turkey, and what other Islamic country did the United States support in the 1950's?": {
        "original_answer": "Morocco",
        "entities": [
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "Pakistan",
            "Turkey,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Islamic country did the United States support in the 1950's?"
    },
    "Along with Americans and Greeks, who has been attacked by November 17, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Turks",
        "entities": [
            "Americans",
            "Greeks"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who has been attacked by November 17, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Abkhazia, what region broke away from Georgia in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "South Ossetia",
        "entities": [
            "Abkhazia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What region broke away from Georgia in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Chevron, what company did Chevron and Caltex merge in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Texaco",
        "entities": [
            "Chevron"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Chevron and Caltex merge in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Mars Polar Lander, what spacecraft failed in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Mars Climate Orbiter",
        "entities": [
            "the Mars Polar Lander"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What spacecraft failed in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the Third International Bering Strait Tunnel, what event will take place in London in September, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Railway Conference",
        "entities": [
            "the Third International Bering Strait Tunnel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What event will take place in London in September, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Belgian and Moroccan troops, what country sent troops to Zaire in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "French",
        "entities": [
            "Belgian",
            "Moroccan troops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country sent troops to Zaire in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with the Pentagon, what city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "New York City",
        "entities": [
            "the Pentagon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Walter Mondale, who was Jackson's opponent in the 1984 election?": {
        "original_answer": "Gary Hart",
        "entities": [
            "Walter Mondale"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was Jackson's opponent in the 1984 election?"
    },
    "Along with Bob Woodward, who wrote articles in 1972 and 1973 describing the leakers who helped Richard Nixon do himself in?": {
        "original_answer": "Carl Bernstein",
        "entities": [
            "Bob Woodward"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who wrote articles in 1972 and 1973 describing the leakers who helped Richard Nixon do himself in?"
    },
    "Along with Keystone, what mountain was asked to leave on July 07, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Mount Rushmore",
        "entities": [
            "Keystone"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What mountain was asked to leave on July 07, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Western diplomats, what country has said the most important physical evidence linking the plot to Iraq is a vehicle that was recovered on April 12, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Kuwaiti",
        "entities": [
            "Western diplomats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has said the most important physical evidence linking the plot to Iraq is a vehicle that was recovered on April 12, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Eritrean separatist guerrillas, who offered divergent peace proposals on February 22, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "The Ethiopian Government",
        "entities": [
            "the Eritrean separatist guerrillas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who offered divergent peace proposals on February 22, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Southern California Edison, who did Judge Lew set a hearing for March 05, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "the California Public Utilities Commission",
        "entities": [
            "Southern California Edison"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Judge Lew set a hearing for March 05, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Natan, who did Shultz meet with September 12, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Avital Sharansky",
        "entities": [
            "Natan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Shultz meet with September 12, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Burton's committee, what other committee held hearings on the Waco incident in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the House Judiciary Committee",
        "entities": [
            "Burton's committee"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other committee held hearings on the Waco incident in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Bertha and Hugo, what hurricane hit Charleston in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Fran",
        "entities": [
            "Bertha",
            "Hugo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What hurricane hit Charleston in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what other republic declared its independence on June 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other republic declared its independence on June 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Enron, what company crashed in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "WorldCom",
        "entities": [
            "Enron"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company crashed in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country struck 100 military and industrial targets in Iraq in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country struck 100 military and industrial targets in Iraq in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, Jordan, Syria and Lebanon, what Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraq",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Jordan",
            "Syria",
            "Lebanon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?"
    },
    "Along with Chad Pennington, who did the Jets lose on January 07, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Jay Fiedler",
        "entities": [
            "Chad Pennington"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Jets lose on January 07, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with The Fiji Sun, what newspaper was closed by soldiers on May 16, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "The Fiji Times",
        "entities": [
            "The Fiji Sun"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper was closed by soldiers on May 16, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with South Korea, who caught North Korea in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States",
        "entities": [
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who caught North Korea in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other country was annexed in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was annexed in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Lithuania, what Baltic state broke away from the Soviet Union in the 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic state broke away from the Soviet Union in the 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country became independent in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country became independent in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with New Brunswick, Prince Edward Island, and what other province did Canada institute a commercial license buy-back program in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Nova Scotia",
        "entities": [
            "New Brunswick",
            "Prince Edward Island,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other province did Canada institute a commercial license buy-back program in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country did Secretary Powell visit in October, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Secretary Powell visit in October, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the US, what other country raided Iraq in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the US"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country raided Iraq in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Zepa, what city was attacked by the Serbs on April 19, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Srebrenica",
        "entities": [
            "Zepa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was attacked by the Serbs on April 19, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country rushed supplies into Chad in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country rushed supplies into Chad in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank and Gaza Strip, what area was annexed by Israel in 1981?": {
        "original_answer": "Golan",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "Gaza Strip"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area was annexed by Israel in 1981?"
    },
    "Along with Davis, who played with the Cadets from 1944 to 1946?": {
        "original_answer": "Blanchard",
        "entities": [
            "Davis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who played with the Cadets from 1944 to 1946?"
    },
    "Along with the British, what country struck 100 military and industrial targets in Iraq in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the British"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country struck 100 military and industrial targets in Iraq in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country will Clinton visit in March, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Bangladesh",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Clinton visit in March, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with CART, what group split in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "I.R.L.",
        "entities": [
            "CART"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group split in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, Gaza, East Jerusalem and East Jerusalem, what was conquered by Israel in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the Golan Heights",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "Gaza",
            "East Jerusalem",
            "East Jerusalem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What was conquered by Israel in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with the US, what other country ordered the ships to be scuttled in the late 1940's?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the US"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country ordered the ships to be scuttled in the late 1940's?"
    },
    "Along with Mhlaba, Mlangeni and Motsoaledi, who was convicted with Mandela in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "Kathrada",
        "entities": [
            "Mhlaba",
            "Mlangeni",
            "Motsoaledi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was convicted with Mandela in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with the Packers, who will the Jets play on December 22, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Favre",
        "entities": [
            "the Packers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who will the Jets play on December 22, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Islamic Holy War, what Islamic group threatened to avenge on January 01, 1997's incident?": {
        "original_answer": "Hamas",
        "entities": [
            "Islamic Holy War"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Islamic group threatened to avenge on January 01, 1997's incident?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, which country exploded nuclear devices in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which country exploded nuclear devices in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and Poland, what former Warsaw Pact member was admitted to NATO in July 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "Poland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Warsaw Pact member was admitted to NATO in July 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan and Kashmir, in what country did the on October 08, 2005 earthquake kill more than 74,000 people?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan",
            "Kashmir",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the on October 08, 2005 earthquake kill more than 74,000 people?"
    },
    "Along with Baquba, what city was bombed on January 27, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Samarra",
        "entities": [
            "Baquba"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was bombed on January 27, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Government in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Government in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Parrett, Vatcher and Murphy, who was Greene acquired from the Atlanta Braves in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Victor Rosario",
        "entities": [
            "Parrett",
            "Vatcher",
            "Murphy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was Greene acquired from the Atlanta Braves in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Mahood, who was killed by British troops on August 21, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Coulter",
        "entities": [
            "Mahood"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed by British troops on August 21, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, Gaza Strip, and what other territory did Israel occupy in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "East Jerusalem",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank",
            "Gaza Strip,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other territory did Israel occupy in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Martin Pearlman, what group will perform at Tanglewood in Lenox, Mass., on June 29, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Boston Baroque",
        "entities": [
            "Martin Pearlman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group will perform at Tanglewood in Lenox, Mass., on June 29, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Thomas Eagleton, who was nominated for vice president in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Sargent Shriver",
        "entities": [
            "Thomas Eagleton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was nominated for vice president in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with the Atlantic, what coast was excluded from the Coastal Resources Barrier Act of 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "Gulf",
        "entities": [
            "the Atlantic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What coast was excluded from the Coastal Resources Barrier Act of 1982?"
    },
    "Along with Maryland, Pennsylvania, Virginia and West Virginia, what other state reported 1,195 rabies cases in raccoons in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "the the District of Columbia",
        "entities": [
            "Maryland",
            "Pennsylvania",
            "Virginia",
            "West Virginia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other state reported 1,195 rabies cases in raccoons in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with MSNBC and NBC, what cable network broadcast more than 375 hours in Salt Lake City in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "CNBC",
        "entities": [
            "MSNBC",
            "NBC"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What cable network broadcast more than 375 hours in Salt Lake City in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the Front, who signed a cease-fire in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "the de Gaulle Government",
        "entities": [
            "the Front"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who signed a cease-fire in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with North Babylon, what high school team did Jones play for in the 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Dix Hills",
        "entities": [
            "North Babylon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What high school team did Jones play for in the 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with Britain and France, what country also signed an agreement with Iran in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Germany",
        "entities": [
            "Britain",
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country also signed an agreement with Iran in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Bread, what theater is performing through December 23, 2001 at the Theater for the New City?": {
        "original_answer": "Puppet Theater",
        "entities": [
            "Bread"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What theater is performing through December 23, 2001 at the Theater for the New City?"
    },
    "Along with the House, what government body established intelligence committees on February 01, 1976?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government body established intelligence committees on February 01, 1976?"
    },
    "Along with the assassinations of John F. Kennedy and Malcolm X, what act was signed in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "the Civil Rights Act",
        "entities": [
            "the assassinations of John F. Kennedy",
            "Malcolm X"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What act was signed in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with Baghdad, what city was bombed by militants on August 01, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Mosul",
        "entities": [
            "Baghdad"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was bombed by militants on August 01, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Ford Motor Company, what company sent a letter to President Clinton on November 10, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "the Chrysler Corporation",
        "entities": [
            "Ford Motor Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company sent a letter to President Clinton on November 10, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Socialists, what group formed a Popular Front government in Paris in 1936?": {
        "original_answer": "Communists",
        "entities": [
            "Socialists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group formed a Popular Front government in Paris in 1936?"
    },
    "Along with the Des Plaines River, what creek was flooded on August 14, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Salt Creek",
        "entities": [
            "the Des Plaines River"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What creek was flooded on August 14, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with France, what country did MySpace open test pages for in September, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Germany",
        "entities": [
            "France"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did MySpace open test pages for in September, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Shiites, who did Washington gamble that a January, 2006 vote would please?": {
        "original_answer": "Kurds",
        "entities": [
            "Shiites"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Washington gamble that a January, 2006 vote would please?"
    },
    "Along with Syria, Saudi Arabia, and the Persian Gulf emirates, what Arab state joined the anti-Iraq alliance in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "and the Persian Gulf emirates"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab state joined the anti-Iraq alliance in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country launched air strikes on Iraq in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country launched air strikes on Iraq in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with West Virginia and Nebraska, what state had primary elections on May 10, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Oklahoma",
        "entities": [
            "West Virginia",
            "Nebraska"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state had primary elections on May 10, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with the House, which chamber has agreed to a deal that would block the Air Force from building combat-ready aircraft in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which chamber has agreed to a deal that would block the Air Force from building combat-ready aircraft in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with the U.S., what country renewed their security treaty in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "Japan",
        "entities": [
            "the U.S."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country renewed their security treaty in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with South African forces, what country entered Angola in 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Cuban",
        "entities": [
            "South African forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country entered Angola in 1975?"
    },
    "Along with Pan Am, on what airline did 140,000 people fly between the two countries in 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Aeroflot",
        "entities": [
            "Pan Am",
            "on"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline did 140,000 people fly between the two countries in 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Ronald B. Stevens, who pleaded guilty on February 05, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Leonard C. Kampf",
        "entities": [
            "Ronald B. Stevens"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who pleaded guilty on February 05, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Ronald Williams, who was killed on the Pine Ridge Indian Reservation in June 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Jack Coler",
        "entities": [
            "Ronald Williams"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed on the Pine Ridge Indian Reservation in June 1975?"
    },
    "Along with the U.S.S. Cole, what embassies were attacked on 11 September 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "East African",
        "entities": [
            "the U.S.S. Cole"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What embassies were attacked on 11 September 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Gareth Wood, who led the expedition to the South Pole in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Roger Mear",
        "entities": [
            "Gareth Wood"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who led the expedition to the South Pole in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with the Taliban and Al Qaeda, who was hunted in Afghanistan on January 21, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Mullah Muhammad Omar",
        "entities": [
            "the Taliban",
            "Al Qaeda"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was hunted in Afghanistan on January 21, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with American cowboys, what gentry settled in Calgary in 1875?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "American cowboys"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What gentry settled in Calgary in 1875?"
    },
    "Along with Tony Blair, who sponsored the peace talks that led to the 1998 agreement?": {
        "original_answer": "Ahern",
        "entities": [
            "Tony Blair"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sponsored the peace talks that led to the 1998 agreement?"
    },
    "Along with Cisco Systems and America Online, what company lost ground on June 21, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Lucent Technologies",
        "entities": [
            "Cisco Systems",
            "America Online"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company lost ground on June 21, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what other country was annexed by the Kremlin in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was annexed by the Kremlin in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Iran, where had a million Kurds fled to in March, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "Iran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where had a million Kurds fled to in March, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Cincinnati Symphony, what other orchestra has Lockhart been an associate conductor of since 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the Cincinnati Pops",
        "entities": [
            "the Cincinnati Symphony"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other orchestra has Lockhart been an associate conductor of since 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country did NATO say it would accept by 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did NATO say it would accept by 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, Bosnia and Macedonia, what other republic broke away from Yugoslavia in the early 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Bosnia",
            "Macedonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other republic broke away from Yugoslavia in the early 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Portugal, what country gained independence in the early 1800's?": {
        "original_answer": "Spain",
        "entities": [
            "Portugal"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country gained independence in the early 1800's?"
    },
    "Along with Alleged Galleries, what architect has a show opening on January 21, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Henry Urbach Architecture",
        "entities": [
            "Alleged Galleries"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What architect has a show opening on January 21, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Hungary, what country did Dole want to be included in the North Atlantic Treaty Organization by 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Dole want to be included in the North Atlantic Treaty Organization by 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Bob Dole, who did George Bush defeat in the 1988 primary?": {
        "original_answer": "Pat Robertson",
        "entities": [
            "Bob Dole"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did George Bush defeat in the 1988 primary?"
    },
    "Along with Fahd al-Quso, who was indicted in New York on May 12, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Jamal Ahmed al-Badawi",
        "entities": [
            "Fahd al-Quso"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in New York on May 12, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Russian, what country's troops occupied Berlin in May 1945?": {
        "original_answer": "Polish",
        "entities": [
            "Russian"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country's troops occupied Berlin in May 1945?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country did Secretary Powell visit in October, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Secretary Powell visit in October, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Martin Luther King Jr., who was killed by a firearm in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Robert Kennedy",
        "entities": [
            "Martin Luther King Jr."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed by a firearm in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Copei, what traditional party wrote the 1961 Constitution?": {
        "original_answer": "Accion Democratica",
        "entities": [
            "Copei"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What traditional party wrote the 1961 Constitution?"
    },
    "Along with the authorities, what group signed an agreement with the communists in April, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Solidarity",
        "entities": [
            "the authorities"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group signed an agreement with the communists in April, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Abdul Fattah Ghandanfar, who was arrested in the October, 1989 raids?": {
        "original_answer": "Hafez Kassem Dalkamoni",
        "entities": [
            "Abdul Fattah Ghandanfar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was arrested in the October, 1989 raids?"
    },
    "Along with the House, what two chambers formed a joint committee to investigate the on September 11, 2004 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two chambers formed a joint committee to investigate the on September 11, 2004 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with Cab Calloway orchestras, who did Ertegun go to see in 1932?": {
        "original_answer": "the Duke Ellington",
        "entities": [
            "Cab Calloway orchestras"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Ertegun go to see in 1932?"
    },
    "Along with the Long Island Orchestra, what group did In Memoriam: Warsaw 1943 belong to?": {
        "original_answer": "Masterworks Chorus",
        "entities": [
            "the Long Island Orchestra"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group did In Memoriam: Warsaw 1943 belong to?"
    },
    "Along with the Federal Bureau of Investigation, who is investigating the 2001 anthrax attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "the Postal Service",
        "entities": [
            "the Federal Bureau of Investigation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who is investigating the 2001 anthrax attacks?"
    },
    "Along with the Kips Bay Boys, what New York club did O'Toole volunteer for in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Girls Club",
        "entities": [
            "the Kips Bay Boys"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What New York club did O'Toole volunteer for in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with I.B.M, what other company is expected to sell 4.6 million Power PC chips in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Motorola",
        "entities": [
            "I.B.M"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company is expected to sell 4.6 million Power PC chips in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with I. Magnin, what other chain was bought by Macy in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Bullock's",
        "entities": [
            "I. Magnin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other chain was bought by Macy in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with August, 1992 Boehm and John Roberts, John Solodar, Tom Smith and George Tornay, who won the deal?": {
        "original_answer": "Alan Miller",
        "entities": [
            "August",
            "1992 Boehm",
            "John Roberts",
            "John Solodar",
            "Tom Smith",
            "George Tornay"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the deal?"
    },
    "Along with British Airways, what airline introduced business-class services in early 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Virgin",
        "entities": [
            "British Airways"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline introduced business-class services in early 2000?"
    },
    "Along with the Middle East, what continent did Stanfield represent Canada in 1979 and 1980?": {
        "original_answer": "North Africa",
        "entities": [
            "the Middle East"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What continent did Stanfield represent Canada in 1979 and 1980?"
    },
    "Along with Kozlowski, who received four special bonuses between 1998 and 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Swartz",
        "entities": [
            "Kozlowski"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who received four special bonuses between 1998 and 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Gaza Strip and East Jerusalem, what territory did Israel occupy in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the Gaza Strip",
            "East Jerusalem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What territory did Israel occupy in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Ni Xiao Ping, who won on June 12, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Ming Jian",
        "entities": [
            "Ni Xiao Ping"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won on June 12, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Luabo and Mopeia, what river town was recaptured by government troops in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Caia",
        "entities": [
            "Luabo",
            "Mopeia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What river town was recaptured by government troops in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the N.A.A.C.P., who sued Yonkers and its Board of Education in 1980?": {
        "original_answer": "the Justice Department",
        "entities": [
            "the N.A.A.C.P."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sued Yonkers and its Board of Education in 1980?"
    },
    "Along with Robert Louis Stevenson and Rudyard Kipling, what adventure novelist was translated into German in the 1890's?": {
        "original_answer": "Jack London",
        "entities": [
            "Robert Louis Stevenson",
            "Rudyard Kipling"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What adventure novelist was translated into German in the 1890's?"
    },
    "Along with Magellan, what probe left for Saturn in 1997) has been described as making up a second golden age of planetary exploration?": {
        "original_answer": "Cassini",
        "entities": [
            "Magellan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What probe left for Saturn in 1997) has been described as making up a second golden age of planetary exploration?"
    },
    "Along with Michael Kors and Marc Jacobs, who was nominated for Women's Wear Designer of 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Carolina Herrera",
        "entities": [
            "Michael Kors",
            "Marc Jacobs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was nominated for Women's Wear Designer of 2004?"
    },
    "Along with ValuJet Flight 592 and what other crash occurred in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "T.W.A. Flight 800",
        "entities": [
            "ValuJet Flight 592"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other crash occurred in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia and Bosnia-Herzogovina, what former Yugoslav republic was recognized by the United States in April, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Bosnia-Herzogovina"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Yugoslav republic was recognized by the United States in April, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Sky Captain, what 2004 sci-fi film depicted robots attacking New York?": {
        "original_answer": "December 06, 2005",
        "entities": [
            "Sky Captain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What 2004 sci-fi film depicted robots attacking New York?"
    },
    "Along with the mausoleum of Sheik Nooruddin Wali, what town was destroyed by fire on May 11, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Charar Sharif",
        "entities": [
            "the mausoleum of Sheik Nooruddin Wali"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What town was destroyed by fire on May 11, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Kamenica, what village was occupied by Yugoslav troops on May 11, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Zogaj",
        "entities": [
            "Kamenica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What village was occupied by Yugoslav troops on May 11, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Florence, what city was devastated by the floods of 1966?": {
        "original_answer": "Venice",
        "entities": [
            "Florence"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was devastated by the floods of 1966?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania and Estonia, what Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Government in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Government in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Osama bin Laden, who was responsible for the 1998 East Africa bombings?": {
        "original_answer": "Al Qaeda",
        "entities": [
            "Osama bin Laden"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was responsible for the 1998 East Africa bombings?"
    },
    "Along with Luxembourg and the Rhineland, what country did Courbet visit in 1858?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "Luxembourg",
            "the Rhineland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Courbet visit in 1858?"
    },
    "Along with the Federal Bureau of Investigation, what agency monitored Leonard Bernstein in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "The Central Intelligence Agency",
        "entities": [
            "the Federal Bureau of Investigation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency monitored Leonard Bernstein in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Robert Polhill and what other hostage was released in April, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Frank Reed",
        "entities": [
            "Robert Polhill"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other hostage was released in April, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Arabs and Turks, who fought in Azerbaijan before the 11th century?": {
        "original_answer": "Khazars",
        "entities": [
            "Arabs",
            "Turks"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who fought in Azerbaijan before the 11th century?"
    },
    "Along with Morocco, Indonesia and Pakistan, what country was bombed in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "Morocco",
            "Indonesia",
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was bombed in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with American Express, who did Mastercard sue on December 02, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Advanta",
        "entities": [
            "American Express"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Mastercard sue on December 02, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Miller Beer and Jacobs Suchard, what company did Philip Morris acquire in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "Kraft General Foods",
        "entities": [
            "Miller Beer",
            "Jacobs Suchard"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Philip Morris acquire in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Long Island, what state did Hurricane Bob damage in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "New England",
        "entities": [
            "Long Island"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state did Hurricane Bob damage in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Pan American, what airline crashed into a mountain on Aug 12, 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "KLM",
        "entities": [
            "Pan American"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline crashed into a mountain on Aug 12, 1985?"
    },
    "Along with Angolans and the South-West Africa People's Organization, what group has been fighting on the site of June 27, 1988's fighting?": {
        "original_answer": "Cubans",
        "entities": [
            "Angolans",
            "the South-West Africa People's Organization"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group has been fighting on the site of June 27, 1988's fighting?"
    },
    "Along with Johnny Paul Koroma, who was indicted in March, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Sam Bockarie",
        "entities": [
            "Johnny Paul Koroma"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in March, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Zoran Djindjic, what politician was assassinated in the Netherlands in May 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Pim Fortuyn",
        "entities": [
            "Zoran Djindjic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What politician was assassinated in the Netherlands in May 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Bryan Adams, Bonnie Raitt, Amy Grant and Natalie Cole, who was nominated for record of 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "R.E.M.",
        "entities": [
            "Bryan Adams",
            "Bonnie Raitt",
            "Amy Grant",
            "Natalie Cole"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was nominated for record of 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the European Council of Churches, what did the Holy Synod withdraw from in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the World Council",
        "entities": [
            "the European Council of Churches"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did the Holy Synod withdraw from in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with The Kansas City Star, what newspaper reported Kerry attended a war group meeting in 1971?": {
        "original_answer": "The New York Sun",
        "entities": [
            "The Kansas City Star"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper reported Kerry attended a war group meeting in 1971?"
    },
    "Along with Leonard Bernstein, Jasper Johns, Frank Gehry and Richard Serra, who won the 2001 Praemium Imperiale Award?": {
        "original_answer": "Ravi Shankar",
        "entities": [
            "Leonard Bernstein",
            "Jasper Johns",
            "Frank Gehry",
            "Richard Serra"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the 2001 Praemium Imperiale Award?"
    },
    "Along with Mohamed Atta, who was a suspect in the September 11, 2001 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "Marwan al-Shehhi",
        "entities": [
            "Mohamed Atta"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a suspect in the September 11, 2001 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with Justice and Justice, what two ministries met in Washington in February, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Finance",
        "entities": [
            "Justice",
            "Justice"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two ministries met in Washington in February, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Chief Superintendent Harry Breen, who was killed on March 20, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Superintendent Bob Buchanan",
        "entities": [
            "Chief Superintendent Harry Breen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed on March 20, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Texaco and Ashland Oil, what company reported earnings on January 24, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Amoco",
        "entities": [
            "Texaco",
            "Ashland Oil"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company reported earnings on January 24, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Parker, who was in Manhattan Central booking on May 07, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Rivers",
        "entities": [
            "Parker"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was in Manhattan Central booking on May 07, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with the Gaza Strip, what lands did Israel occupy in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "the Gaza Strip"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What lands did Israel occupy in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with John McCarthy, what hostage was released by Israel on August 23, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Edward Austin Tracy",
        "entities": [
            "John McCarthy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What hostage was released by Israel on August 23, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, what Arab state participated in a peace conference in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab state participated in a peace conference in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia and Kosovo, what wars did Sir Richard handle in the 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Bosnia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Kosovo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What wars did Sir Richard handle in the 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country tested nuclear weapons in May, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country tested nuclear weapons in May, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia and Yugoslavia's other four republics, what other republic was recognized by the European Community on January 15, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Yugoslavia's other four republics"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other republic was recognized by the European Community on January 15, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with other Warsaw Pact forces, who ''invited'' to suppress the Prague Spring in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Soviet",
        "entities": [
            "other Warsaw Pact forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who ''invited'' to suppress the Prague Spring in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Nicaragua, El Salvador, Honduras and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Guatemala",
        "entities": [
            "Nicaragua",
            "El Salvador",
            "Honduras",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Neptune, what planet will Voyager II encounter on August 24, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Triton",
        "entities": [
            "Neptune"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What planet will Voyager II encounter on August 24, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Hungarians, what ethnic group was stripped of their Czechoslovak citizenship in 1945?": {
        "original_answer": "Germans",
        "entities": [
            "Hungarians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group was stripped of their Czechoslovak citizenship in 1945?"
    },
    "Along with LSF-KEB Holdings, who was indicted on November 20, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Korea Exchange",
        "entities": [
            "LSF-KEB Holdings"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted on November 20, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Cyrus Vance, who was Lord of Bosnian Serbs in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Owen",
        "entities": [
            "Cyrus Vance"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was Lord of Bosnian Serbs in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with J. D. Bernal, what Cambridge scientist was a member of Dr. Needham's group in the 1930's?": {
        "original_answer": "Julian Huxley",
        "entities": [
            "J. D. Bernal"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Cambridge scientist was a member of Dr. Needham's group in the 1930's?"
    },
    "Along with the Santa Ysabel, what race did Sweet Catomine win in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "the Santa Anita Oaks",
        "entities": [
            "the Santa Ysabel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did Sweet Catomine win in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what other country seceded from Yugoslavia in June 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country seceded from Yugoslavia in June 1991?"
    },
    "Along with some commuter airlines, what did People Express buy in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Frontier Airlines",
        "entities": [
            "some commuter airlines"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did People Express buy in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Toyota, McLaren-Mercedes and Williams-BMW, which team has spent more than $400 million in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Ferrari",
        "entities": [
            "Toyota",
            "McLaren-Mercedes",
            "Williams-BMW"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which team has spent more than $400 million in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Razgrad and Kirdzhali, what northern city saw demonstrations for January 09, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Kolarovgrad",
        "entities": [
            "Razgrad",
            "Kirdzhali"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What northern city saw demonstrations for January 09, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Cuba and Angola, what country signed a peace agreement in December, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "South Africa",
        "entities": [
            "Cuba",
            "Angola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in December, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Neptune, what other planet was made public on August 24, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Triton",
        "entities": [
            "Neptune"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other planet was made public on August 24, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with St. Louis, what city backed Al Gore in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Kansas City",
        "entities": [
            "St. Louis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city backed Al Gore in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Guadeloupe, Martinique, and what other French department did Paris incorporate in 1946?": {
        "original_answer": "French Guiana",
        "entities": [
            "Guadeloupe",
            "Martinique,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other French department did Paris incorporate in 1946?"
    },
    "Along with the Yangtze, what river roared out of its banks in 1931?": {
        "original_answer": "Huai Rivers",
        "entities": [
            "the Yangtze"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What river roared out of its banks in 1931?"
    },
    "Along with Compaq, what company did Towbin work for in the 1970's and 80's?": {
        "original_answer": "Intel",
        "entities": [
            "Compaq"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Towbin work for in the 1970's and 80's?"
    },
    "Along with Muslim, who is to rule Ilidza in March, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatian",
        "entities": [
            "Muslim"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who is to rule Ilidza in March, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country divided Kashmir in 1947?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country divided Kashmir in 1947?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country had a nuclear explosion in May 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistani",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country had a nuclear explosion in May 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Catherine Comet and Jahja Ling, who won the prize in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Neal Stulberg",
        "entities": [
            "Catherine Comet",
            "Jahja Ling"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the prize in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the Federated States of Micronesia, what country gained independence in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Marshalls",
        "entities": [
            "the Federated States of Micronesia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country gained independence in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with Tony Martin, who did Mr. Coles and Mr. Atkins perform with in 1955?": {
        "original_answer": "Pearl Bailey",
        "entities": [
            "Tony Martin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Mr. Coles and Mr. Atkins perform with in 1955?"
    },
    "Along with Syria and Tunisia, what country met with Qaddafi on May 28, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Algeria",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "Tunisia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country met with Qaddafi on May 28, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Peter F. Cohalan, who approved land purchases in 1980?": {
        "original_answer": "the County Legislature",
        "entities": [
            "Peter F. Cohalan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who approved land purchases in 1980?"
    },
    "Along with Sports Illustrated, what network started a sports news network in December, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "CNN",
        "entities": [
            "Sports Illustrated"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What network started a sports news network in December, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the Russians, what country killed about 25,000 sperm whales a year in the Pacific in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "Japanese",
        "entities": [
            "the Russians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country killed about 25,000 sperm whales a year in the Pacific in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Kroto and Smalley, who won the 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry?": {
        "original_answer": "Curl",
        "entities": [
            "Kroto",
            "Smalley"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry?"
    },
    "Along with pneumonia, what did Dr. Cahill say Bernstein suffered from earlier in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "pleurisy",
        "entities": [
            "pneumonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did Dr. Cahill say Bernstein suffered from earlier in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Indonesia, what country signed an agreement with the United Nations on May 05, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Portugal",
        "entities": [
            "Indonesia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with the United Nations on May 05, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Exxon Mobil, what company did Saudi Aramco sign a deal with in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Sinopec",
        "entities": [
            "Exxon Mobil"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Saudi Aramco sign a deal with in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Jack Coler, who was killed on the Pine Ridge Indian Reservation in June 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Ronald Williams",
        "entities": [
            "Jack Coler"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed on the Pine Ridge Indian Reservation in June 1975?"
    },
    "Along with the Grand National Mosque, what university was located in Islamabad in 1971?": {
        "original_answer": "the University of Islamabad",
        "entities": [
            "the Grand National Mosque"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What university was located in Islamabad in 1971?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with South Africa, Cuba and the Uited States, what country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Angola",
        "entities": [
            "South Africa",
            "Cuba",
            "the Uited States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace agreement in December, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Senator Moynihan, who negotiated a compromise with House members in April, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Alfonse M. D'Amato",
        "entities": [
            "Senator Moynihan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who negotiated a compromise with House members in April, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Astoria, Ravenswood and Dutch Kills, what village joined together in 1870?": {
        "original_answer": "Hunters Point",
        "entities": [
            "Astoria",
            "Ravenswood",
            "Dutch Kills"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What village joined together in 1870?"
    },
    "Along with the Nonproliferation Treaty, what country signed an agreement with Pyongyang in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "South Korea",
        "entities": [
            "the Nonproliferation Treaty"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with Pyongyang in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Japanese, who killed about 25,000 sperm whales a year in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "Russians",
        "entities": [
            "the Japanese"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who killed about 25,000 sperm whales a year in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, what country will the Israeli Philharmonic tour in October, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will the Israeli Philharmonic tour in October, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the creation of a single European market by the end of 1992, what free-trade agreement was cited as potentially dangerous for world trade?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States-Canada",
        "entities": [
            "the creation of a single European market by the end of 1992"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What free-trade agreement was cited as potentially dangerous for world trade?"
    },
    "Along with Georgia, Alabama and what other state, at least 13 people died in floods by March, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Florida",
        "entities": [
            "Georgia",
            "Alabama"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other state, at least 13 people died in floods by March, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with John Henry, who was elected to the United States Senate in 1789?": {
        "original_answer": "Charles Carroll",
        "entities": [
            "John Henry"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was elected to the United States Senate in 1789?"
    },
    "Along with Lady and the Tramp, what other Disney film was withdrawn in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Cinderella",
        "entities": [
            "Lady",
            "the Tramp"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Disney film was withdrawn in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Coulter, who was killed by British troops on August 21, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Mahood",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Coulter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed by British troops on August 21, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Daddo, who became the world's fastest sailors in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "McKeon",
        "entities": [
            "Daddo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who became the world's fastest sailors in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the House, what other chamber passed a compromise version of a bill in May, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other chamber passed a compromise version of a bill in May, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Milosevic, what party was the Serbian Radical Party voted out of office in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbian Socialist Party",
        "entities": [
            "Milosevic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What party was the Serbian Radical Party voted out of office in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Kuwait, what country did 163 Americans leave on December 09, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraq",
        "entities": [
            "Kuwait"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did 163 Americans leave on December 09, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Ricky Martin and David Bowie, who is the Matrix working with May, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Britney Spears",
        "entities": [
            "Ricky Martin",
            "David Bowie"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who is the Matrix working with May, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Hamas, what Islamic group threatened to avenge on January 01, 1997's incident?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamic Holy War",
        "entities": [
            "Hamas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Islamic group threatened to avenge on January 01, 1997's incident?"
    },
    "Along with NASA, what government agency studied beaming microwave power during the energy crisis of the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Department of Energy",
        "entities": [
            "NASA"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government agency studied beaming microwave power during the energy crisis of the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Nicaragua, Guatemala, Honduras and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "El Salvador",
        "entities": [
            "Nicaragua",
            "Guatemala",
            "Honduras",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the Blue Shield Association of America, what organization issued guidelines in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "the Blue Cross",
        "entities": [
            "the Blue Shield Association of America"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization issued guidelines in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the Library of Congress, what other federal agency has declared 2001 the first year of the 21st century?": {
        "original_answer": "the National Institute of Standards and Technology",
        "entities": [
            "the Library of Congress"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other federal agency has declared 2001 the first year of the 21st century?"
    },
    "Along with what district, Tuckahoe filed suit over the same issue in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Hampton Bays",
        "entities": [
            ""
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What district, Tuckahoe filed suit over the same issue in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Planned Parenthood, what state will ask the Supreme Court to strike down regulations imposed in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "the State of New York",
        "entities": [
            "Planned Parenthood"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state will ask the Supreme Court to strike down regulations imposed in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with British agents, what country arrested five people on March 28, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "British agents"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country arrested five people on March 28, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Pure Food and Drug Act of 1906, what law did Roosevelt pass?": {
        "original_answer": "the Meat Inspection Act",
        "entities": [
            "the Pure Food",
            "Drug Act of 1906"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What law did Roosevelt pass?"
    },
    "Along with the Round Valley, what reservoir in the central part of the state was built after the 1964-65 drought?": {
        "original_answer": "Spruce Run Reservoirs",
        "entities": [
            "the Round Valley"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What reservoir in the central part of the state was built after the 1964-65 drought?"
    },
    "Along with Stuyvesant Town, what apartment complex sold for a record-breaking $5.4 billion in November, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Peter Cooper Village",
        "entities": [
            "Stuyvesant Town"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What apartment complex sold for a record-breaking $5.4 billion in November, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Envergure of France, Holiday Inn and what other hotel developer, Euro Disney has signed deals to build 2,000 rooms by 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Marriott",
        "entities": [
            "Envergure of France",
            "Holiday Inn"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other hotel developer, Euro Disney has signed deals to build 2,000 rooms by 2004?"
    },
    "Along with the Honda Motor Company, what company offered incentives in November 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Ford",
        "entities": [
            "the Honda Motor Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company offered incentives in November 1992?"
    },
    "Along with a hard-line political party, what group urged Iranians to participate in a rally after August 13, 2004 Prayer?": {
        "original_answer": "Revolutionary Guards",
        "entities": [
            "a hard-line political party"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group urged Iranians to participate in a rally after August 13, 2004 Prayer?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and the Czech Republic, what country did NATO admit to the summit meeting in July, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did NATO admit to the summit meeting in July, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what other Baltic republic lost their independence in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic lost their independence in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with AOL Time Warner, which company did Homestore count on bogus deals with in 2000 and 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Cendant",
        "entities": [
            "AOL Time Warner"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Which company did Homestore count on bogus deals with in 2000 and 2001?"
    },
    "Along with two Chinese engineers, who was kidnapped on October 09, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistanis",
        "entities": [
            "two Chinese engineers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was kidnapped on October 09, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Saudi Arabia, what two countries tightened their pressure on Iraq on November 06, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "The United States",
        "entities": [
            "Saudi Arabia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two countries tightened their pressure on Iraq on November 06, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Santa Anita Oaks, what race did Sweet Catomine win in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "the Santa Ysabel",
        "entities": [
            "the Santa Anita Oaks"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did Sweet Catomine win in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Bosnia and Macedonia, what former Yugoslav state declared independence in the early 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Bosnia",
            "Macedonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Yugoslav state declared independence in the early 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank town of Jericho, where did the Palestine Liberation Organization take control of in May, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank town of Jericho"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did the Palestine Liberation Organization take control of in May, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Catholics, what group was a party to the April 14, 2006 peace accords?": {
        "original_answer": "Protestants",
        "entities": [
            "Catholics"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group was a party to the April 14, 2006 peace accords?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Hungary, what other country joined NATO in April, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country joined NATO in April, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Sony, what other major game console maker is preparing to launch a 360 in 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Nintendo",
        "entities": [
            "Sony"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other major game console maker is preparing to launch a 360 in 2006?"
    },
    "Along with the Long Island Rail Road, what railroad was crippled by a snowstorm in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the Metro-North Railroad",
        "entities": [
            "the Long Island Rail Road"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What railroad was crippled by a snowstorm in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Eastern traditions, what traditions are re-creating the great furniture classics of 18th-century Europe and early America?": {
        "original_answer": "Western",
        "entities": [
            "Eastern traditions"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What traditions are re-creating the great furniture classics of 18th-century Europe and early America?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what other former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with National Public Radio, what news network covered the events of September 11, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "ABC News",
        "entities": [
            "National Public Radio"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What news network covered the events of September 11, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with an Australian, what nationality was killed in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Belgian",
        "entities": [
            "an Australian"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What nationality was killed in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Cambodia and Indochina, what country did ''Bitter Victory'' travel to in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "Vietnam",
        "entities": [
            "Cambodia",
            "Indochina"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did ''Bitter Victory'' travel to in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Honduras, Guatemala and Costa Rica, what country joined Nicaragua in the agreement announced on February 21, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "El Salvador",
        "entities": [
            "Honduras",
            "Guatemala",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined Nicaragua in the agreement announced on February 21, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Turkey, what country did the Kurds flee to in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Iran",
        "entities": [
            "Turkey"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the Kurds flee to in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Khalid al-Midhar and what other hijacker did Sufaat meet in January 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Nawaq Alhazmi",
        "entities": [
            "Khalid al-Midhar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other hijacker did Sufaat meet in January 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Lithuania, what Baltic republic was admitted to the General Assembly in September, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was admitted to the General Assembly in September, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Kurdish, what political group abandoned negotiations with Sunnis on August 26, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Shiite",
        "entities": [
            "Kurdish"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political group abandoned negotiations with Sunnis on August 26, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Vance and Eve, who was killed on Feb. 9, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Eve Dingman",
        "entities": [
            "Vance",
            "Eve"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed on Feb. 9, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Ebbets Field, the fourth Polo Grounds, and the third Garden, what stadium was built from 1911 to 1925?": {
        "original_answer": "Yankee Stadium",
        "entities": [
            "Ebbets Field",
            "the fourth Polo Grounds",
            "and the third Garden"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What stadium was built from 1911 to 1925?"
    },
    "Along with Vladimir and Pero Skopljak, who surrendered on October 07, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Ivan Santic",
        "entities": [
            "Vladimir",
            "Pero Skopljak"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who surrendered on October 07, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with loyalist groups, what group has killed 33 people in Northern Ireland in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "I.R.A.",
        "entities": [
            "loyalist groups"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group has killed 33 people in Northern Ireland in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Goldman Sachs, what investment fund managed 25 Wyndham hotels in March, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Highgate Holdings",
        "entities": [
            "Goldman Sachs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What investment fund managed 25 Wyndham hotels in March, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with the Conservative Book Club, what publishing company did McCaffrey founded in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "Arlington House Publishers",
        "entities": [
            "the Conservative Book Club"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What publishing company did McCaffrey founded in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with the Uzi, what semiautomatic weapon was banned by the City Council on February 07, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "AK-47",
        "entities": [
            "the Uzi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What semiautomatic weapon was banned by the City Council on February 07, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Accel Partners and Menlo Ventures, what venture capital firm invested in UUNet in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "New Enterprise Associates",
        "entities": [
            "Accel Partners",
            "Menlo Ventures"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What venture capital firm invested in UUNet in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia and Croatia, what group did the International Olympic Committee recognize in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "republics",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia",
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group did the International Olympic Committee recognize in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Hungary, what former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in July 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in July 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Miles and Chiron Corporation, what company won a legal round on February 24, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Genentech",
        "entities": [
            "Miles",
            "Chiron Corporation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company won a legal round on February 24, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Modigliani, Chagall and what other artist was sold at auction in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Kandinsky",
        "entities": [
            "Modigliani",
            "Chagall"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other artist was sold at auction in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Bulgaria, what country supported the invasion of Czechoslovakia in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "East Germany",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Bulgaria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country supported the invasion of Czechoslovakia in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Marilyn, what hurricane damaged St. Croix in September, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Luis",
        "entities": [
            "Marilyn"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What hurricane damaged St. Croix in September, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Spain, what country split South America in the early 1800's?": {
        "original_answer": "Portugal",
        "entities": [
            "Spain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country split South America in the early 1800's?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what republic declared its independence in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What republic declared its independence in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Galicia and Bohemia, from 1860 to 1910, Jews migrated from what country to Vienna?": {
        "original_answer": "Moravia",
        "entities": [
            "Galicia",
            "Bohemia",
            "from 1860 to 1910",
            "Jews migrated from"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country to Vienna?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what country declared independence on June 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country declared independence on June 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Derby, what other race did Unbridled win in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "the Breeders' Cup Classic",
        "entities": [
            "the Derby"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other race did Unbridled win in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Trans World Airlines, what airline announced fare cuts on August 13, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Eastern Airlines",
        "entities": [
            "Trans World Airlines"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline announced fare cuts on August 13, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Bolivia, what country is a party to the 1961 Single Convention on Narcotic Drugs?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States",
        "entities": [
            "Bolivia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country is a party to the 1961 Single Convention on Narcotic Drugs?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what Baltic nation was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic nation was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Belgian and French troops, what country supplied supplies to Zaire in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "Belgian",
            "French troops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country supplied supplies to Zaire in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with the Meat Inspection Act, what other act was passed in 1906?": {
        "original_answer": "the Pure Food and Drug Act",
        "entities": [
            "the Meat Inspection Act"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other act was passed in 1906?"
    },
    "Along with Coltrane, the Modern Jazz Quartet, and Ornette Coleman, what jazz musician joined Atlantic in 1956?": {
        "original_answer": "Charles Mingus",
        "entities": [
            "Coltrane",
            "the Modern Jazz Quartet",
            "and Ornette Coleman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What jazz musician joined Atlantic in 1956?"
    },
    "Along with Richard M. Nixon, who was the Libertarian candidate in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Spiro T. Agnew",
        "entities": [
            "Richard M. Nixon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was the Libertarian candidate in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with the Taurus, what Ford car was the top selling car in the United States in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Sable",
        "entities": [
            "the Taurus"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Ford car was the top selling car in the United States in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Robert F. Kennedy, who was assassinated in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Martin Luther King Jr.",
        "entities": [
            "Robert F. Kennedy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was assassinated in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with nationalists, what political party won a surprise victory in the December, 1993 elections?": {
        "original_answer": "Communists",
        "entities": [
            "nationalists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party won a surprise victory in the December, 1993 elections?"
    },
    "Along with Mick Jagger, who signed Tosh to their own label in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Keith Richards",
        "entities": [
            "Mick Jagger"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who signed Tosh to their own label in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with the Urhobo, what ethnic group was fighting on January 31, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Itsekiri",
        "entities": [
            "the Urhobo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group was fighting on January 31, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia and any of Yugoslavia's other four republics, what country was recognized by the European Community on January 15, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia",
            "any of Yugoslavia's other four republics"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was recognized by the European Community on January 15, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with I.B.M., what company did Apple enter an alliance with in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Motorola",
        "entities": [
            "I.B.M."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Apple enter an alliance with in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Prague, what city sponsored a Rudolf exhibition in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Vienna",
        "entities": [
            "Prague"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city sponsored a Rudolf exhibition in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with the Veracruz Blues, what team did Ray Dandridge play for in the 1940's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Mexico City Red Devils",
        "entities": [
            "the Veracruz Blues"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What team did Ray Dandridge play for in the 1940's?"
    },
    "Along with the United Nations, with what country did Habibie sign a on May 05, 1999 agreement?": {
        "original_answer": "Portugal",
        "entities": [
            "the United Nations",
            "with"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Habibie sign a on May 05, 1999 agreement?"
    },
    "Along with Lahore, in what city did violence flare on February 13, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamabad",
        "entities": [
            "Lahore",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city did violence flare on February 13, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Mozart, what composer will Leonard Bernstein conduct on August 15, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Sibelius",
        "entities": [
            "Mozart"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What composer will Leonard Bernstein conduct on August 15, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what republics were incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Baltic",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What republics were incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with All Nippon Airways and Japan Air System, what airline successfully completed their Year 2000 computer tests?": {
        "original_answer": "Japan Airlines",
        "entities": [
            "All Nippon Airways",
            "Japan Air System"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline successfully completed their Year 2000 computer tests?"
    },
    "Along with the Small Business Administration, what military branch was involved in a negotiating session in 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "Army",
        "entities": [
            "the Small Business Administration"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What military branch was involved in a negotiating session in 1982?"
    },
    "Along with Gaza and the West Bank, what country will Clinton visit on December 12, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Israel",
        "entities": [
            "Gaza",
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Clinton visit on December 12, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Protestants, who signed a peace agreement with Northern Ireland in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Catholics",
        "entities": [
            "Protestants"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who signed a peace agreement with Northern Ireland in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Martin Gilenas, Petr Klima and Joe Murphy, who did the Oilers use in the 1990 Stanley Cup?": {
        "original_answer": "Adam Graves",
        "entities": [
            "Martin Gilenas",
            "Petr Klima",
            "Joe Murphy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Oilers use in the 1990 Stanley Cup?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Guinness, who was a Sinn Fein leader in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Adams",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Guinness"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a Sinn Fein leader in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Afghanistan, in what country did violence erupt on February 09, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "Afghanistan",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did violence erupt on February 09, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Acre, who will be sworn into office on January 01, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Xapuri",
        "entities": [
            "Acre"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who will be sworn into office on January 01, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Parkview Hilton, what Hartford hotel closed in 1990 due to lack of business?": {
        "original_answer": "Summit",
        "entities": [
            "Parkview Hilton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Hartford hotel closed in 1990 due to lack of business?"
    },
    "Along with Fiat and Olivetti, what Italian company was founded in the 19th century?": {
        "original_answer": "Pirelli",
        "entities": [
            "Fiat",
            "Olivetti"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Italian company was founded in the 19th century?"
    },
    "Along with CBS, what tennis association did USA recently work with to present the Open for 1989 and 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "the United States Tennis Association",
        "entities": [
            "CBS"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What tennis association did USA recently work with to present the Open for 1989 and 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviet Union, what country divided Armenian lands in 1920?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviet Union"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country divided Armenian lands in 1920?"
    },
    "Along with the de Gaulle Government, what group signed a cease-fire in 1962?": {
        "original_answer": "Front",
        "entities": [
            "the de Gaulle Government"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group signed a cease-fire in 1962?"
    },
    "Along with James Stewart, who starred in Alfred Hitchcock's 1956 film THE MAN WHO KNEW TOO MUCH?": {
        "original_answer": "Doris Day",
        "entities": [
            "James Stewart"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who starred in Alfred Hitchcock's 1956 film THE MAN WHO KNEW TOO MUCH?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country did the alliance accept in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the alliance accept in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Guatemala, El Salvador, Honduras and Costa Rica, what country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Nicaragua",
        "entities": [
            "Guatemala",
            "El Salvador",
            "Honduras",
            "Costa Rica"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a peace plan in August, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Montenegro, what GATT member did the United States withdraw from the GATT in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbia",
        "entities": [
            "Montenegro"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What GATT member did the United States withdraw from the GATT in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with India, what country tested nuclear weapons in May, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Pakistan",
        "entities": [
            "India"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country tested nuclear weapons in May, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other Baltic republic lost its independence in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic lost its independence in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country destroyed military installations in Iraq in December, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country destroyed military installations in Iraq in December, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with NBC, on what other network did ''Columbo Phile'' air from 1971 to 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "ABC",
        "entities": [
            "NBC",
            "on"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other network did ''Columbo Phile'' air from 1971 to 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Central Committee, what other body collapsed on December 03, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Politburo",
        "entities": [
            "the Central Committee"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other body collapsed on December 03, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Inwood, what district has 24 people running in April 30, 1996's election?": {
        "original_answer": "Washington Heights",
        "entities": [
            "Inwood"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What district has 24 people running in April 30, 1996's election?"
    },
    "Along with Martin Luther King Jr., who was assassinated in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Robert F. Kennedy",
        "entities": [
            "Martin Luther King Jr."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was assassinated in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Dr Devious, Selkirk, and Sheikh Albadou, who won the Breeders' Cup in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Zoman",
        "entities": [
            "Dr Devious",
            "Selkirk",
            "and Sheikh Albadou"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the Breeders' Cup in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with The New York Sun, what newspaper reported Kerry attended a war group meeting in Kansas City in 1971?": {
        "original_answer": "The Kansas City Star",
        "entities": [
            "The New York Sun"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper reported Kerry attended a war group meeting in Kansas City in 1971?"
    },
    "Along with Palestinian officials, what country did Ross meet with December 23, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Israeli",
        "entities": [
            "Palestinian officials"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Ross meet with December 23, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with East Timor, what forces laid waste to East Timor after East Timorese voted to separate from Indonesia in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Indonesian",
        "entities": [
            "East Timor"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What forces laid waste to East Timor after East Timorese voted to separate from Indonesia in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the World Trade Center, what other building was attacked in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Pentagon",
        "entities": [
            "the World Trade Center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other building was attacked in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what other country did Kohl promise to recognize by December 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Kohl promise to recognize by December 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Muslim, what other religious group protested the Bush administration's handling of October 08, 1990's disturbances at holy places in Jerusalem?": {
        "original_answer": "Jewish",
        "entities": [
            "Muslim"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other religious group protested the Bush administration's handling of October 08, 1990's disturbances at holy places in Jerusalem?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and Hungary, what country did the alliance take in in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Czech Republic",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the alliance take in in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the National Institute of Standards and Technology, what federal agency declared 2001 the first year of the 21st century?": {
        "original_answer": "the Library of Congress",
        "entities": [
            "the National Institute of Standards",
            "Technology"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What federal agency declared 2001 the first year of the 21st century?"
    },
    "Along with commercial aviation, what military branch phased out JP-4 in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Navy",
        "entities": [
            "commercial aviation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What military branch phased out JP-4 in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with British Airways, what airline retired its Concorde fleet in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Air France",
        "entities": [
            "British Airways"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline retired its Concorde fleet in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Gen. Ratko Mladic, what Bosnian Serb leader was indicted in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Radovan Karadzic",
        "entities": [
            "Gen. Ratko Mladic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Bosnian Serb leader was indicted in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Carlos Chavez and Benjamin Lees, what 20th century composer wrote music for Mr. Szeryng?": {
        "original_answer": "Michael Ponce",
        "entities": [
            "Carlos Chavez",
            "Benjamin Lees"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What 20th century composer wrote music for Mr. Szeryng?"
    },
    "Along with the PLO, what country signed an agreement in Washington in September, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Israel",
        "entities": [
            "the PLO"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement in Washington in September, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Oscar, what novel did Mr. Carey win the prize for in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Lucinda",
        "entities": [
            "Oscar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What novel did Mr. Carey win the prize for in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Condoleezza Rice, who was a witness in the September 11, 2004 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "Richard A. Clarke",
        "entities": [
            "Condoleezza Rice"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a witness in the September 11, 2004 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with Yugoslavia, Croatia and what other country has Dienstbier been investigating since 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Bosnia-Herzegovina",
        "entities": [
            "Yugoslavia",
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country has Dienstbier been investigating since 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Jordan, Iraq, Syria and Lebanon, what Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Jordan",
            "Iraq",
            "Syria",
            "Lebanon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?"
    },
    "Along with Grace Kelly, who did John Lund appear with in films in the 1940's and 50's?": {
        "original_answer": "Olivia de Havilland, Marlene Dietrich",
        "entities": [
            "Grace Kelly"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did John Lund appear with in films in the 1940's and 50's?"
    },
    "Along with Virginia, West Virginia and what other state, miners struck Pittston's coal mining operations on April 05, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Kentucky",
        "entities": [
            "Virginia",
            "West Virginia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other state, miners struck Pittston's coal mining operations on April 05, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Byelorussia, what country joins the 1968 nuclear non-proliferation treaty?": {
        "original_answer": "Ukraine",
        "entities": [
            "Byelorussia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joins the 1968 nuclear non-proliferation treaty?"
    },
    "Along with the International Opera of Havana, what opera did Newman sing with in the 1940's?": {
        "original_answer": "the St. Louis Chamber Opera",
        "entities": [
            "the International Opera of Havana"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What opera did Newman sing with in the 1940's?"
    },
    "Along with Ukraine, what republic joined the 1968 nuclear non-proliferation treaty?": {
        "original_answer": "Byelorussia",
        "entities": [
            "Ukraine"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What republic joined the 1968 nuclear non-proliferation treaty?"
    },
    "Along with Sony Entertainment, 989 Studios, Sega, and Microsoft, what company produced football games in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Electronic Arts",
        "entities": [
            "Sony Entertainment",
            "989 Studios",
            "Sega",
            "and Microsoft"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company produced football games in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Amsterdam's Bar, what restaurant opened on the Upper West Side in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "Rotisserie",
        "entities": [
            "Amsterdam's Bar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What restaurant opened on the Upper West Side in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Moldavia, what Baltic republic was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Moldavia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Barbara Gladstone, who produced ''in March, 1997 with the Anal Sadistic Warrior''?": {
        "original_answer": "Barney",
        "entities": [
            "Barbara Gladstone"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who produced ''in March, 1997 with the Anal Sadistic Warrior''?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia's national guard, what country was fighting for a October 06, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbian",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia's national guard"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was fighting for a October 06, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Lithuanian parliament, what country's parliament voted for independence in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvian",
        "entities": [
            "the Lithuanian parliament"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country's parliament voted for independence in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what Baltic country gained independence in August 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country gained independence in August 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Tutsi, what other group was killed in Rwanda in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Hutu",
        "entities": [
            "the Tutsi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other group was killed in Rwanda in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Inwood Development Corporation, what nonprofit organization was started in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "The Washington Heights",
        "entities": [
            "Inwood Development Corporation"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What nonprofit organization was started in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with Voltaire, who sat for Marie Antoinette in 1783 and 1778?": {
        "original_answer": "Benjamin Franklin",
        "entities": [
            "Voltaire"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who sat for Marie Antoinette in 1783 and 1778?"
    },
    "Along with Tiffany Roberts, who was a member of the United States Olympic soccer team in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Cindy Parlow",
        "entities": [
            "Tiffany Roberts"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a member of the United States Olympic soccer team in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Pakistan, what country had a nuclear explosion in May 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Indian",
        "entities": [
            "Pakistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country had a nuclear explosion in May 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Iran, what other country had a coup engineered by the Central Intelligence Agency in the 1950's?": {
        "original_answer": "Guatemala",
        "entities": [
            "Iran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country had a coup engineered by the Central Intelligence Agency in the 1950's?"
    },
    "Along with Mercedes and AEG, what company suffered huge losses in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "DASA",
        "entities": [
            "Mercedes",
            "AEG"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company suffered huge losses in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Bristol and West Haven, what Connecticut city had an Eastern League team in the 1970's and 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Waterbury",
        "entities": [
            "Bristol",
            "West Haven"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Connecticut city had an Eastern League team in the 1970's and 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, what newspaper tried to resume publication on August 03, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "The Pittsburgh Press",
        "entities": [
            "the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper tried to resume publication on August 03, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Norway, what other country joined the European Union on January 01, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Austria",
        "entities": [
            "Norway"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country joined the European Union on January 01, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Kisangani, Kenge and what other strategic city was captured in May, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Lubumbashi",
        "entities": [
            "Kisangani",
            "Kenge"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other strategic city was captured in May, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Israel, what country was attacked by Iraqi missiles during the Persian Gulf war in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Saudi Arabia",
        "entities": [
            "Israel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was attacked by Iraqi missiles during the Persian Gulf war in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the National Institutes of Health, what organization is attempting to produce a complete, archival sequence of human DNA by 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "the Sanger Center",
        "entities": [
            "the National Institutes of Health"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization is attempting to produce a complete, archival sequence of human DNA by 2005?"
    },
    "Along with the Pentagon, what building was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "the World Trade Center",
        "entities": [
            "the Pentagon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What building was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, Latvia and what other Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the Czech Republic and Hungary, what former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in July 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "the Czech Republic",
            "Hungary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Warsaw Pact nation joined NATO in July 1999?"
    },
    "Along with WorldCom, what company crashed in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Enron",
        "entities": [
            "WorldCom"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company crashed in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with the Communists, what group proposed that the first free legislative elections should take place in November, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Agrarians",
        "entities": [
            "the Communists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group proposed that the first free legislative elections should take place in November, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Viaduct do Cha, what was revitalized between 1992 and 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Patriarch Plaza",
        "entities": [
            "Viaduct do Cha"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What was revitalized between 1992 and 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Archer, who was freed on April 23, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Scherzers",
        "entities": [
            "Archer"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was freed on April 23, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Arafat, who did the hard-line factions of the P.L.O. fight in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "Abu Jihad",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Arafat"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the hard-line factions of the P.L.O. fight in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Turkey and Morocco, what country was bombed in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Indonesia",
        "entities": [
            "Turkey",
            "Morocco"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was bombed in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Joseph Abboud, what luxury label did Mr. Ginsburg introduce in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Hugo Boss",
        "entities": [
            "Joseph Abboud"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What luxury label did Mr. Ginsburg introduce in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what other country seceded from Yugoslavia in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country seceded from Yugoslavia in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what country declared independence from Yugoslavia in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country declared independence from Yugoslavia in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Britain and what other country, the Greek tribunal reviewed the case on December 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Netherlands",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country, the Greek tribunal reviewed the case on December 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Croats and Muslims, what ethnic group fought in the Yugoslavian wars in the 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbs",
        "entities": [
            "Croats",
            "Muslims"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group fought in the Yugoslavian wars in the 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Julius Erving, who played in the 1977 N.B.A. finals?": {
        "original_answer": "Bill Walton",
        "entities": [
            "Julius Erving"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who played in the 1977 N.B.A. finals?"
    },
    "Along with Montgomery Ward & Company, what three retailers have signed deals with carriers in 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Sears, Roebuck & Company",
        "entities": [
            "Montgomery Ward & Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What three retailers have signed deals with carriers in 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Arkansas and Tennessee, what state was hit by tornadoes on April 17, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Kentucky",
        "entities": [
            "Arkansas",
            "Tennessee"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state was hit by tornadoes on April 17, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Yeltsin, who signed the 1970 pact?": {
        "original_answer": "George Bush",
        "entities": [
            "Yeltsin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who signed the 1970 pact?"
    },
    "Along with British Airways, what airline announced that the Concorde would be shutting down in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Air France",
        "entities": [
            "British Airways"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline announced that the Concorde would be shutting down in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Abraham & Straus, what other store was added to Macy's East division in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan Marsh",
        "entities": [
            "Abraham & Straus"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other store was added to Macy's East division in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Morgan Grenfell and First Bank of Boston, what investment bank arrived in Lubumbashi on May 10, 1997 to begin negotiations with rebels?": {
        "original_answer": "Goldman Sachs",
        "entities": [
            "Morgan Grenfell",
            "First Bank of Boston"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What investment bank arrived in Lubumbashi on May 10, 1997 to begin negotiations with rebels?"
    },
    "Along with Myers, who did A-Rod join in getting rings in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Damon",
        "entities": [
            "Myers"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did A-Rod join in getting rings in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Satwant Singh, who was executed on January 06, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Kehar Singh",
        "entities": [
            "Satwant Singh"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was executed on January 06, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what small independent nation did Moscow take control of in 1939 and 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What small independent nation did Moscow take control of in 1939 and 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Montenegro, what team does the Ivory Coast take on on June 21, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbia",
        "entities": [
            "Montenegro"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What team does the Ivory Coast take on on June 21, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with President Bush, what political party won the on November 05, 2002 election?": {
        "original_answer": "Republicans",
        "entities": [
            "President Bush"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party won the on November 05, 2002 election?"
    },
    "Along with Sensitive Prince and Affirmed, who won the Triple Crown in 1978?": {
        "original_answer": "Alydar",
        "entities": [
            "Sensitive Prince",
            "Affirmed"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the Triple Crown in 1978?"
    },
    "Along with New Brunswick, Nova Scotia and what other province did Canada institute a commercial license buy-back program in 1986?": {
        "original_answer": "Prince Edward Island",
        "entities": [
            "New Brunswick",
            "Nova Scotia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other province did Canada institute a commercial license buy-back program in 1986?"
    },
    "Along with the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, what group is scheduled to strike on June 30, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "The Screen Actors Guild",
        "entities": [
            "the American Federation of Television",
            "Radio Artists"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group is scheduled to strike on June 30, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with the Wood Memorial, what race did he win in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the Florida Derby",
        "entities": [
            "the Wood Memorial"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What race did he win in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Sci-Fi Channel, what entertainment network was purchased from Mr. Diller in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "the USA Network",
        "entities": [
            "Sci-Fi Channel"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What entertainment network was purchased from Mr. Diller in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Carnegie, what foundation published reports in 1959 proposing ways to reform business and management training at college and university levels?": {
        "original_answer": "Ford Foundations",
        "entities": [
            "Carnegie"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What foundation published reports in 1959 proposing ways to reform business and management training at college and university levels?"
    },
    "Along with Racine and Janesville, what Wisconsin city did he represent in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Kenosha",
        "entities": [
            "Racine",
            "Janesville"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Wisconsin city did he represent in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with the Russians, what other country invaded Central Asia in the 19th century?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the Russians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country invaded Central Asia in the 19th century?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and what other Baltic state, Lithuania broke from the Soviet Union in the 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic state, Lithuania broke from the Soviet Union in the 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Cameroon, what other territory did Cameroon become independent of in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "French African",
        "entities": [
            "Cameroon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other territory did Cameroon become independent of in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with Czechs, what other group marched in Prague in August, 1988 to mark the 20th anniversary of the invasion of the Soviet Union?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovaks",
        "entities": [
            "Czechs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other group marched in Prague in August, 1988 to mark the 20th anniversary of the invasion of the Soviet Union?"
    },
    "Along with NBC, who did the NBA sign a deal with on November 11, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Turner Sports",
        "entities": [
            "NBC"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the NBA sign a deal with on November 11, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what other nation was Lithuania annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Baltic",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other nation was Lithuania annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the Croatian minority, what other minority did Baker say was concerned about rights abuses in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbian",
        "entities": [
            "the Croatian minority"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other minority did Baker say was concerned about rights abuses in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Pentagon, what US landmark was targeted on September 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "the World Trade Center",
        "entities": [
            "the Pentagon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What US landmark was targeted on September 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Castellano, who was killed by the F.B.I. in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Bilotti",
        "entities": [
            "Castellano"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed by the F.B.I. in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with Day, who did John Cort meet in 1936?": {
        "original_answer": "Maurin",
        "entities": [
            "Day"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did John Cort meet in 1936?"
    },
    "Along with Jimmie Dale Gilmore and Butch Hancock, who was a member of the Flatlanders in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Joe Ely",
        "entities": [
            "Jimmie Dale Gilmore",
            "Butch Hancock"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a member of the Flatlanders in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with the World Trade Center, what other building was damaged by the September 11, 2003 attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "Pentagon",
        "entities": [
            "the World Trade Center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other building was damaged by the September 11, 2003 attacks?"
    },
    "Along with French officials, what other country hopes to open Mont Blanc by 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Italian",
        "entities": [
            "French officials"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country hopes to open Mont Blanc by 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Yugoslav Army, what rebels did the Croats fight in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Serb",
        "entities": [
            "the Yugoslav Army"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What rebels did the Croats fight in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Macedonia and Slovenia, what country broke away from Yugoslavia in the early 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Bosnia",
        "entities": [
            "Macedonia",
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country broke away from Yugoslavia in the early 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with New York, what other city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Washington",
        "entities": [
            "New York"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other city was attacked on Sept. 11, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with the Throgs Neck, where were two couples spotted nesting in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "Verrazano-Narrows Bridges",
        "entities": [
            "the Throgs Neck"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where were two couples spotted nesting in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Jerusalem's walled core, what city was in Jordanian hands in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "Bethlehem",
        "entities": [
            "Jerusalem's walled core"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was in Jordanian hands in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with Tunisians, who was arrested in Belgium on November 26, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Algerians",
        "entities": [
            "Tunisians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was arrested in Belgium on November 26, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Eales, who was part of the Australian team that won the World Cup in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Tim Horan",
        "entities": [
            "Eales"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was part of the Australian team that won the World Cup in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Hornwood, what company had combined net assets of about $1.6 billion at September, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Oriental",
        "entities": [
            "Hornwood"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company had combined net assets of about $1.6 billion at September, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Croats, what ethnic group believes that Milosevic is ready to talk about rewriting the 1974 constitution?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenes",
        "entities": [
            "Croats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group believes that Milosevic is ready to talk about rewriting the 1974 constitution?"
    },
    "Along with Andrew Goodman, James E. Chaney and what other civil rights worker was killed in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "Michael H. Schwerner",
        "entities": [
            "Andrew Goodman",
            "James E. Chaney"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other civil rights worker was killed in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with Kristi Yamaguchi and Nancy Kerrigan, who won the world figure skating championships in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Tonya Harding",
        "entities": [
            "Kristi Yamaguchi",
            "Nancy Kerrigan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the world figure skating championships in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Orange County, what state did he vow to win in November, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "California",
        "entities": [
            "Orange County"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state did he vow to win in November, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the F.B.I., what Kenyan organization searched bin Laden's house in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "C.I.A.",
        "entities": [
            "the F.B.I."
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Kenyan organization searched bin Laden's house in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Senegal, what two countries formed a confederation in the 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Gambia",
        "entities": [
            "Senegal"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two countries formed a confederation in the 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with the French, what country's embassy was bombed in 1983?": {
        "original_answer": "American",
        "entities": [
            "the French"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country's embassy was bombed in 1983?"
    },
    "Along with Tanzania, in what country did embassy bombings occur in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Kenya",
        "entities": [
            "Tanzania",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did embassy bombings occur in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the Central Intelligence Agency, what agency monitored Leonard Bernstein in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Federal Bureau of Investigation",
        "entities": [
            "the Central Intelligence Agency"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency monitored Leonard Bernstein in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Shankaranand, who was a major figure in the 1992 financial scandal?": {
        "original_answer": "Thakur",
        "entities": [
            "Shankaranand"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a major figure in the 1992 financial scandal?"
    },
    "Along with CBS Telenoticias, what Brazilian cable network is expected to begin broadcasting in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Eco",
        "entities": [
            "CBS Telenoticias"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Brazilian cable network is expected to begin broadcasting in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Fidelity Investments, what organization conducted a survey in March, 1993 about I.R.A.'s?": {
        "original_answer": "the Gallup Organization",
        "entities": [
            "Fidelity Investments"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization conducted a survey in March, 1993 about I.R.A.'s?"
    },
    "Along with the Czech Republic, what country did the alliance take in in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the alliance take in in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the Manhattan Mayhem, what team will be joined in June, 2005 by the Queens of Pain?": {
        "original_answer": "the Brooklyn Bombshells",
        "entities": [
            "the Manhattan Mayhem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What team will be joined in June, 2005 by the Queens of Pain?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, Bosnia and Macedonia, what former Yugoslav state declared independence in the early 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Bosnia",
            "Macedonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former Yugoslav state declared independence in the early 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Israel, from what country did Fellah say hundreds of Libyan Jews would visit their native country in July, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Europe",
        "entities": [
            "Israel",
            "from"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Fellah say hundreds of Libyan Jews would visit their native country in July, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what country in the north declared its independence in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country in the north declared its independence in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Hamas, what Palestinian faction fought for supremacy on June 12, 2007?": {
        "original_answer": "Fatah",
        "entities": [
            "Hamas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Palestinian faction fought for supremacy on June 12, 2007?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, Hungary and Bulgaria, what country held a summit meeting in Warsaw in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "East Germany",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "Hungary",
            "Bulgaria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country held a summit meeting in Warsaw in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what Baltic state regained their independence in August, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic state regained their independence in August, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Maritime Telecommunications Network, what company is expected to announce similar agreements with other cruise lines in December, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "AT&T",
        "entities": [
            "Maritime Telecommunications Network"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company is expected to announce similar agreements with other cruise lines in December, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Serbs, Croats and Yugoslavia, what nation was founded in Dubrovnik in 1918?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenes",
        "entities": [
            "Serbs",
            "Croats",
            "Yugoslavia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What nation was founded in Dubrovnik in 1918?"
    },
    "Along with the Israeli army, who said Zatma had organized a 1995 suicide bombing at a bus stop?": {
        "original_answer": "Islamic Jihad",
        "entities": [
            "the Israeli army"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who said Zatma had organized a 1995 suicide bombing at a bus stop?"
    },
    "Along with Scythopolis, what new name did Beit Shean acquire in the fourth century B.C.?": {
        "original_answer": "Nysa",
        "entities": [
            "Scythopolis"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What new name did Beit Shean acquire in the fourth century B.C.?"
    },
    "Along with Washington, who made concessions to the cease-fire agreement in 1973?": {
        "original_answer": "Hanoi",
        "entities": [
            "Washington"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who made concessions to the cease-fire agreement in 1973?"
    },
    "Along with the United States and Britain, what country signed away the occupation rights of sovereignty in their zones of Germany from 1952 to 1955?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed away the occupation rights of sovereignty in their zones of Germany from 1952 to 1955?"
    },
    "Along with Lebanon, in what country did attacks on civilians cease on April 27, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Israel",
        "entities": [
            "Lebanon",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did attacks on civilians cease on April 27, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Elements 107 and 109, what other element was discovered by G.S.I. from 1981 to 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "108",
        "entities": [
            "Elements 107",
            "109"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other element was discovered by G.S.I. from 1981 to 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Ieng Sary, who was sentenced to death in Cambodia in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "Pol Pot",
        "entities": [
            "Ieng Sary"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was sentenced to death in Cambodia in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Radovan Karadzic, what Bosnian Serb leader was indicted in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Ratko Mladic",
        "entities": [
            "Radovan Karadzic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Bosnian Serb leader was indicted in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Lincoln and Jaguar, what division of Ford sold 406.991 cars and light trucks in June, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Mercury",
        "entities": [
            "Lincoln",
            "Jaguar"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What division of Ford sold 406.991 cars and light trucks in June, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the Mediterranean, what seas burst into the Black Sea in 5600 B.C.?": {
        "original_answer": "Aegean",
        "entities": [
            "the Mediterranean"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What seas burst into the Black Sea in 5600 B.C.?"
    },
    "Along with The Spectator, what newspaper did Grigg write for after The Guardian closed in 1960?": {
        "original_answer": "Times",
        "entities": [
            "The Spectator"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper did Grigg write for after The Guardian closed in 1960?"
    },
    "Along with New York, what state approved a cleanup plan in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Connecticut",
        "entities": [
            "New York"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state approved a cleanup plan in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Somalia and Sudan, what Arab country had diplomatic relations with Egypt in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "Oman",
        "entities": [
            "Somalia",
            "Sudan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country had diplomatic relations with Egypt in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Brazil and Uruguay, what country has signed an agreement that is supposed to open its borders to one another by the beginning of 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Argentina",
        "entities": [
            "Brazil",
            "Uruguay"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has signed an agreement that is supposed to open its borders to one another by the beginning of 1996?"
    },
    "Along with East Timor, in what other country did the killings continue on September 13, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "West Timor",
        "entities": [
            "East Timor",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did the killings continue on September 13, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with the Dutch, what country occupied Gibraltar in 1704?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the Dutch"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country occupied Gibraltar in 1704?"
    },
    "Along with Syria and Iraq, what country boycotted Jordan in 1958?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "Iraq"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country boycotted Jordan in 1958?"
    },
    "Along with the courts, what government body did Fujimori shut down in April, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Congress",
        "entities": [
            "the courts"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government body did Fujimori shut down in April, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with St. Croix, what island was St. Thomas sold to the United States in 1917?": {
        "original_answer": "St. John",
        "entities": [
            "St. Croix"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What island was St. Thomas sold to the United States in 1917?"
    },
    "Along with Vietnam and Yemen, what country pulled non-aligned nations to the left in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Algeria",
        "entities": [
            "Vietnam",
            "Yemen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country pulled non-aligned nations to the left in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with Robert Moses, who was the baron that reorganized Moscow in the 1930's?": {
        "original_answer": "Haussmann",
        "entities": [
            "Robert Moses"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was the baron that reorganized Moscow in the 1930's?"
    },
    "Along with Alan Kulwicki, who died in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Davey Allison",
        "entities": [
            "Alan Kulwicki"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who died in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Protestant paramilitary groups and security forces, what group has killed 3,167 people since 1969?": {
        "original_answer": "I.R.A.",
        "entities": [
            "Protestant paramilitary groups",
            "security forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group has killed 3,167 people since 1969?"
    },
    "Along with General Foods and Nabisco Holdings, what company did Philip Morris buy in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Kraft",
        "entities": [
            "General Foods",
            "Nabisco Holdings"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Philip Morris buy in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what other country bombed Iraq in late 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country bombed Iraq in late 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Charles Rubia and what other politician was arrested in July, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Kenneth Matiba",
        "entities": [
            "Charles Rubia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other politician was arrested in July, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and the Czech Republic, what other country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country received $30 million from the Pentagon in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Joe Hartsoe, who did Abraham meet with on March 29, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Linda Robertson",
        "entities": [
            "Joe Hartsoe"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Abraham meet with on March 29, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Rockland Utilities, what company did Con Edison acquire in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Orange",
        "entities": [
            "Rockland Utilities"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company did Con Edison acquire in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Muslim forces, who was fighting in Sarajevo on May 10, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Serbian",
        "entities": [
            "Muslim forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was fighting in Sarajevo on May 10, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Duke Ellington, what orchestra did Ertegun go to see in 1932?": {
        "original_answer": "Cab Calloway",
        "entities": [
            "Duke Ellington"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What orchestra did Ertegun go to see in 1932?"
    },
    "Along with Harlem, what other city has Farrell represented since 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "Washington Heights",
        "entities": [
            "Harlem"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other city has Farrell represented since 1975?"
    },
    "Along with Luxembourg, Austria, Ireland, Finland and Portugal, what country adopted the euro in January 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Belgium",
        "entities": [
            "Luxembourg",
            "Austria",
            "Ireland",
            "Finland",
            "Portugal"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country adopted the euro in January 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Dave Johnson, who was the chief architect of Salt Lake City's bid to acquire the 2002 Winter Olympics?": {
        "original_answer": "Tom Welch",
        "entities": [
            "Dave Johnson"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was the chief architect of Salt Lake City's bid to acquire the 2002 Winter Olympics?"
    },
    "Along with Poland, East Germany and Bulgaria, what country invaded Czechoslovakia in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "East Germany",
            "Bulgaria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country invaded Czechoslovakia in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Tiger Woods, who won the British Open in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Tom Lehman",
        "entities": [
            "Tiger Woods"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won the British Open in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Providence Equity Partners, what company bought PanAmSat in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "the Carlyle Group",
        "entities": [
            "Providence Equity Partners"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company bought PanAmSat in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Leipzig, Chemnitz and what other city, where there were protests on July 05, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Erfurt",
        "entities": [
            "Leipzig",
            "Chemnitz"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other city, where there were protests on July 05, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Iran, what country did the Kurds flee to in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkey",
        "entities": [
            "Iran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the Kurds flee to in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Navy Seals, who carried out the on January 23, 2002 raid?": {
        "original_answer": "Army Special Forces",
        "entities": [
            "Navy Seals"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who carried out the on January 23, 2002 raid?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Bush, what Republican party won the 2004 presidential election?": {
        "original_answer": "Congressional",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Bush"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Republican party won the 2004 presidential election?"
    },
    "Along with Kenya, in what country did Al Qaeda bomb US Embassies in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Tanzania",
        "entities": [
            "Kenya",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Al Qaeda bomb US Embassies in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Toyota, what company announced the Czech venture in December, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Peugeot",
        "entities": [
            "Toyota"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company announced the Czech venture in December, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Mullah Muhammad Omar, Taliban and Al Qaeda fighters, who was hunted in Afghanistan on January 21, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "Osama bin Laden",
        "entities": [
            "Mullah Muhammad Omar",
            "Taliban",
            "Al Qaeda fighters"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was hunted in Afghanistan on January 21, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Meola, who was an integral part of the American team in the 1990 and 1994 World Cups?": {
        "original_answer": "Wynalda",
        "entities": [
            "Meola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was an integral part of the American team in the 1990 and 1994 World Cups?"
    },
    "Along with Morocco, what country signed several agreements in the early 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Algeria",
        "entities": [
            "Morocco"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed several agreements in the early 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Heinrich Strubig, who did Picco hope would be released by December 25, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Thomas Kemptner",
        "entities": [
            "Heinrich Strubig"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Picco hope would be released by December 25, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Joe Lieberman, who did the Stand for Israel fellowship honor in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Rudy Giuliani",
        "entities": [
            "Joe Lieberman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Stand for Israel fellowship honor in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with the International Federation of Film Archives, what other organization was Franju involved with from 1938 to 1953?": {
        "original_answer": "the Institute of Scientific Cinematography",
        "entities": [
            "the International Federation of Film Archives"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other organization was Franju involved with from 1938 to 1953?"
    },
    "Along with the House, what committee passed legislation aimed at putting payments in farmers' hands by September, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Senate Agriculture Committees",
        "entities": [
            "the House"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What committee passed legislation aimed at putting payments in farmers' hands by September, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Eduardo Costa and John Perrault, who organized a wild fashion show and poetry reading in 1969?": {
        "original_answer": "Hannah Weiner",
        "entities": [
            "Eduardo Costa",
            "John Perrault"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who organized a wild fashion show and poetry reading in 1969?"
    },
    "Along with Sumgait, what Azerbaijani city saw violence on March 01, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Kirovabad",
        "entities": [
            "Sumgait"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Azerbaijani city saw violence on March 01, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with California and New Jersey, what state passed legislation in 2004 to prohibit the sale of DXM-containing cough and cold medications to minors?": {
        "original_answer": "New York",
        "entities": [
            "California",
            "New Jersey"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state passed legislation in 2004 to prohibit the sale of DXM-containing cough and cold medications to minors?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania and Estonia, what other country was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was incorporated into the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Hungary and the Czech Republic, what country did the alliance accept in July 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Hungary",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did the alliance accept in July 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Syria and the Arab League, what country was reluctant to criticize an Arab brother in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Egypt",
        "entities": [
            "Syria",
            "the Arab League"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was reluctant to criticize an Arab brother in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Brandon Haw, who did the Jets sign on August 02, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Roosevelt Williams",
        "entities": [
            "Brandon Haw"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did the Jets sign on August 02, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with The New York Times, what newspaper did Mr. Bart work for from the late 1950's to 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "The Wall Street Journal",
        "entities": [
            "The New York Times"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What newspaper did Mr. Bart work for from the late 1950's to 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Baader, Raspe, and what other woman committed suicide in Stammheim in 1977?": {
        "original_answer": "Ensslin",
        "entities": [
            "Baader",
            "Raspe,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other woman committed suicide in Stammheim in 1977?"
    },
    "Along with masked Serbs, who blocked roads in Sarajevo on March 02, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Croats",
        "entities": [
            "masked Serbs"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who blocked roads in Sarajevo on March 02, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Sam Bockarie, who was indicted in March, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Johnny Paul Koroma",
        "entities": [
            "Sam Bockarie"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in March, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with the Department of Energy, what government agency studied beaming microwave power during the energy crisis of the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "NASA",
        "entities": [
            "the Department of Energy"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government agency studied beaming microwave power during the energy crisis of the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with the Regents and Team 100, who did Mr. Bush thank for supporting in the 2000 election?": {
        "original_answer": "the Republican Party",
        "entities": [
            "the Regents",
            "Team 100"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Mr. Bush thank for supporting in the 2000 election?"
    },
    "Along with the Malawi Government, what organization did the United Nations assist in organizing the June 1993 national referendum?": {
        "original_answer": "the National Constitutional Council",
        "entities": [
            "the Malawi Government"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization did the United Nations assist in organizing the June 1993 national referendum?"
    },
    "Along with Japan and South Korea, what country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "China",
        "entities": [
            "Japan",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with La Caravelle, what restaurant closed for good in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Lut\u00e8ce",
        "entities": [
            "La Caravelle"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What restaurant closed for good in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Kronenbourg and Gervais-Danone, what brewery did BSN acquire in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "Kanterbrau",
        "entities": [
            "Kronenbourg",
            "Gervais-Danone"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What brewery did BSN acquire in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with Mercedes-Benz, what company offered discount-leasing plans in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "the Ford Motor Company",
        "entities": [
            "Mercedes-Benz"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company offered discount-leasing plans in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with the United States and Britain, what country set up a safe haven in northern Iraq in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "France",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country set up a safe haven in northern Iraq in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Bulgaria and East Germany, what country supported the invasion of Czechoslovakia in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Poland",
        "entities": [
            "Bulgaria",
            "East Germany"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country supported the invasion of Czechoslovakia in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Robert Thompson, who was killed in Liverpool in February, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Jon Venables",
        "entities": [
            "Robert Thompson"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed in Liverpool in February, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Abiola, who was killed in the August 01, 1998 election?": {
        "original_answer": "General Abacha",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Abiola"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed in the August 01, 1998 election?"
    },
    "Along with Russia and what other country did Christianity come to Russia in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Ukraine",
        "entities": [
            "Russia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country did Christianity come to Russia in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Chevron Canada Resources, what company drilled a well on Newfoundland's Grand Banks in 1979?": {
        "original_answer": "Petro-Canada",
        "entities": [
            "Chevron Canada Resources"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company drilled a well on Newfoundland's Grand Banks in 1979?"
    },
    "Along with Andrew Goodman, Michael H. Schwerner and what other civil rights worker was killed in 1964?": {
        "original_answer": "James E. Chaney",
        "entities": [
            "Andrew Goodman",
            "Michael H. Schwerner"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other civil rights worker was killed in 1964?"
    },
    "Along with the Blue Cross, what organization issued guidelines for coverage of preventive services in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Blue Shield Association of America",
        "entities": [
            "the Blue Cross"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization issued guidelines for coverage of preventive services in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the Postal Service, what agency continues to investigate the 2001 anthrax attacks?": {
        "original_answer": "the Federal Bureau of Investigation",
        "entities": [
            "the Postal Service"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency continues to investigate the 2001 anthrax attacks?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country signed a treaty banning biological weapons in 1972?": {
        "original_answer": "the Soviet Union",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a treaty banning biological weapons in 1972?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what area was closed off on December 13, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area was closed off on December 13, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with New Jersey and New York State, what state signed a nonaggression pact in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Connecticut",
        "entities": [
            "New Jersey",
            "New York State"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state signed a nonaggression pact in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Kansas, what state was hit by a tornado on May 03, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Oklahoma",
        "entities": [
            "Kansas"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state was hit by a tornado on May 03, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Lithuania, what Baltic state regained their independence in August, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic state regained their independence in August, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what country walked out in 1985?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country walked out in 1985?"
    },
    "Along with Time magazine, what media outlet ran a poll in March, 1995 showing Powell as the second most popular Republican candidate?": {
        "original_answer": "CNN",
        "entities": [
            "Time magazine"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What media outlet ran a poll in March, 1995 showing Powell as the second most popular Republican candidate?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviet Union, what country recognized the Democratic Republic of Vietnam in February 1950?": {
        "original_answer": "China",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviet Union"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country recognized the Democratic Republic of Vietnam in February 1950?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Estonia, what country was forcibly occupied by the Soviet Union in June 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was forcibly occupied by the Soviet Union in June 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what two Yugoslavia's richest republics declared themselves independent on July 02, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What two Yugoslavia's richest republics declared themselves independent on July 02, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Islamic Jihad, what group took responsibility for August 09, 2001's terrorism?": {
        "original_answer": "Hamas",
        "entities": [
            "Islamic Jihad"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group took responsibility for August 09, 2001's terrorism?"
    },
    "Along with Keir Dullea, who stars in 2001: A SPACE ODYSSEY?": {
        "original_answer": "Gary Lockwood",
        "entities": [
            "Keir Dullea"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who stars in 2001: A SPACE ODYSSEY?"
    },
    "Along with British Petroleum, what Norwegian state oil company is expected to invest $350 million by 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Statoil",
        "entities": [
            "British Petroleum"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Norwegian state oil company is expected to invest $350 million by 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Cambodia, what country did President Nixon expand the fighting into in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Laos",
        "entities": [
            "Cambodia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did President Nixon expand the fighting into in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with the Democratic Party, what political party has Tisch been working with to bring conventions to New York in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Republican",
        "entities": [
            "the Democratic Party"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party has Tisch been working with to bring conventions to New York in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with the Dodge Aries, what K-car was instrumental in Chrysler's financial recovery in the early 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Plymouth Reliant",
        "entities": [
            "the Dodge Aries"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What K-car was instrumental in Chrysler's financial recovery in the early 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with Venezuela's spy service, what agency did Posada serve in the 1960's and 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Central Intelligence Agency",
        "entities": [
            "Venezuela's spy service"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What agency did Posada serve in the 1960's and 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other country will Russian troops be out of on August 31, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country will Russian troops be out of on August 31, 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Serb civilians, what country's police were fighting on July 07, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatian",
        "entities": [
            "Serb civilians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country's police were fighting on July 07, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Betty Bronson and Ernest Torrence, who starred in the 1924 version of Peter Pan?": {
        "original_answer": "May, 1998",
        "entities": [
            "Betty Bronson",
            "Ernest Torrence"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who starred in the 1924 version of Peter Pan?"
    },
    "Along with the World Bank and Unaids, what organization did Farmer go to in 1998, 1999, and 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "the World Health Organization",
        "entities": [
            "the World Bank",
            "Unaids"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization did Farmer go to in 1998, 1999, and 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Turner Sports, what network did the NBA sign a deal with on November 11, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "NBC",
        "entities": [
            "Turner Sports"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What network did the NBA sign a deal with on November 11, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Garth H. Drabinsky, who was indicted in Canada in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Myron I. Gottlieb",
        "entities": [
            "Garth H. Drabinsky"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in Canada in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Hughes Electronics, what company helped China improve the guidance, telemetry and aerodynamics of the Long in March, 2003 rockets?": {
        "original_answer": "Boeing",
        "entities": [
            "Hughes Electronics"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company helped China improve the guidance, telemetry and aerodynamics of the Long in March, 2003 rockets?"
    },
    "Along with Omar Torrijos, who was the president of Panama between 1968 and 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Manuel Noriega",
        "entities": [
            "Omar Torrijos"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was the president of Panama between 1968 and 1989?"
    },
    "Along with the United States, what other country signed a treaty in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "the Soviet Union",
        "entities": [
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country signed a treaty in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Poles and Hungarians, what other country was admitted to NATO in March, 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Czechs",
        "entities": [
            "Poles",
            "Hungarians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was admitted to NATO in March, 1999?"
    },
    "Along with New Mexico and Colorado, what state did Adams visit with O'Keeffe in 1937?": {
        "original_answer": "Arizona",
        "entities": [
            "New Mexico",
            "Colorado"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state did Adams visit with O'Keeffe in 1937?"
    },
    "Along with Poland and the Czech Republic, what country did NATO admit to the summit meeting in July, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Hungary",
        "entities": [
            "Poland",
            "the Czech Republic"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did NATO admit to the summit meeting in July, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with East Asia and the United States, what continent did Bawa travel to in 1946?": {
        "original_answer": "Europe",
        "entities": [
            "East Asia",
            "the United States"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What continent did Bawa travel to in 1946?"
    },
    "Along with Barbara Walters, who did ABC try to install non-white anchors in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Max Robinson",
        "entities": [
            "Barbara Walters"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did ABC try to install non-white anchors in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with the Authors Guild, what organization sent an open letter to Jeff Bezos in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "the Association of American Publishers",
        "entities": [
            "the Authors Guild"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization sent an open letter to Jeff Bezos in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Bangladesh, what country will Clinton visit in March, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "India",
        "entities": [
            "Bangladesh"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Clinton visit in March, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Rwanda, what country invaded Congo in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Uganda",
        "entities": [
            "Rwanda"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country invaded Congo in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Rakim, who was featured on the 1988 Nassau Veterans Memorial Coliseum show?": {
        "original_answer": "Eric B.",
        "entities": [
            "Rakim"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was featured on the 1988 Nassau Veterans Memorial Coliseum show?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, where did Davison play in January, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Switzerland",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Where did Davison play in January, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Prince Sihanouk's forces, what group did China tell them it would not provide them with any more money or weapons in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Son Sann",
        "entities": [
            "Prince Sihanouk's forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group did China tell them it would not provide them with any more money or weapons in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Chechens, what group was deported to Central Asia in 1944?": {
        "original_answer": "Ingush",
        "entities": [
            "Chechens"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group was deported to Central Asia in 1944?"
    },
    "Along with Slovenia, what other country declared its independence in June, 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country declared its independence in June, 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Gary Hart, who was Jackson's opponent in the 1984 election?": {
        "original_answer": "Walter Mondale",
        "entities": [
            "Gary Hart"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was Jackson's opponent in the 1984 election?"
    },
    "Along with Carlos Alberto Costa, who won a judgment against Cuba in 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Mario M. de la Pe\u00f1a",
        "entities": [
            "Carlos Alberto Costa"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who won a judgment against Cuba in 1997?"
    },
    "Along with the Royal Green Jackets, what British military unit was bombed in London in 1982?": {
        "original_answer": "the Household Cavalry",
        "entities": [
            "the Royal Green Jackets"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What British military unit was bombed in London in 1982?"
    },
    "Along with the Ford Motor Company, what other company's buyer-incentive programs expired on September 30, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "the General Motors Corporation",
        "entities": [
            "the Ford Motor Company"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other company's buyer-incentive programs expired on September 30, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with Duzce, what city was devastated by the August, 1999 quake?": {
        "original_answer": "Bolu",
        "entities": [
            "Duzce"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city was devastated by the August, 1999 quake?"
    },
    "Along with Taco Bell and Pizza Hut, what chain did Pepsico spin off on October 07, 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "the Kendrtucky Fried Chicken",
        "entities": [
            "Taco Bell",
            "Pizza Hut"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What chain did Pepsico spin off on October 07, 1997?"
    },
    "Along with the Mackenzie, Peace and what other river did Steger kayak in 1969?": {
        "original_answer": "Yukon Rivers",
        "entities": [
            "the Mackenzie",
            "Peace"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other river did Steger kayak in 1969?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Lithuania, what Baltic country gained independence in August 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic country gained independence in August 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Cincinnati Pops, what orchestra has Lockhart been the associate conductor of since 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the Cincinnati Symphony",
        "entities": [
            "the Cincinnati Pops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What orchestra has Lockhart been the associate conductor of since 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Ford, what company offered incentives in November 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the Honda Motor Company",
        "entities": [
            "Ford"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company offered incentives in November 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what other country was recognized by the Vatican on January 14, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was recognized by the Vatican on January 14, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Yerkes Observatory, what university did Professor Stromgren associate with in 1936?": {
        "original_answer": "the University of Chicago",
        "entities": [
            "Yerkes Observatory"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What university did Professor Stromgren associate with in 1936?"
    },
    "Along with St. Louis, Atlanta and Detroit, what Michigan assembly plant did Ford shut down in January, 2006?": {
        "original_answer": "Wixom",
        "entities": [
            "St. Louis",
            "Atlanta",
            "Detroit"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Michigan assembly plant did Ford shut down in January, 2006?"
    },
    "Along with Turkey, Persia and Britain, what country contested the mountains of Central Asia in the early 1800's?": {
        "original_answer": "Russia",
        "entities": [
            "Turkey",
            "Persia",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country contested the mountains of Central Asia in the early 1800's?"
    },
    "Along with Massimo, who designed a lithograph of a 1970 New York City subway map?": {
        "original_answer": "Lella Vignelli",
        "entities": [
            "Massimo"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who designed a lithograph of a 1970 New York City subway map?"
    },
    "Along with Mussolini, who was poised to take over Europe in 1939?": {
        "original_answer": "Hitler",
        "entities": [
            "Mussolini"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was poised to take over Europe in 1939?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what area did ISRAEL acquire in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "Gaza Strip",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What area did ISRAEL acquire in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with the Huai River, what river killed 225,000 people in 1931?": {
        "original_answer": "Yangtze",
        "entities": [
            "the Huai River"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What river killed 225,000 people in 1931?"
    },
    "Along with President Mikhail S. Gorbachev, what Soviet body denounced Lithuania's on March 11, 1990 declaration of independence?": {
        "original_answer": "Congress",
        "entities": [
            "President Mikhail S. Gorbachev"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Soviet body denounced Lithuania's on March 11, 1990 declaration of independence?"
    },
    "Along with Hughes Counties, what county was hit by fires on December 27, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Seminole",
        "entities": [
            "Hughes Counties"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What county was hit by fires on December 27, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with New Mexico and Arizona, what state did Adams visit with O'Keeffe in 1937?": {
        "original_answer": "Colorado",
        "entities": [
            "New Mexico",
            "Arizona"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state did Adams visit with O'Keeffe in 1937?"
    },
    "Along with Azerbaijan, what country did Rumsfeld visit on December 15, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Armenia",
        "entities": [
            "Azerbaijan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Rumsfeld visit on December 15, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Prague, in what city did Russian tanks crush uprisings in 1956 and 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Budapest",
        "entities": [
            "Prague",
            "in"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What city did Russian tanks crush uprisings in 1956 and 1968?"
    },
    "Along with Kurds, what group launched twin uprisings in Iraq in March, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Shiites",
        "entities": [
            "Kurds"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group launched twin uprisings in Iraq in March, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with liberals and blacks, what group helped save Silver from a coup in 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "Hispanic Democrats",
        "entities": [
            "liberals",
            "blacks"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group helped save Silver from a coup in 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Cuban forces, what country entered Angola in 1975?": {
        "original_answer": "South African",
        "entities": [
            "Cuban forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country entered Angola in 1975?"
    },
    "Along with Meola and Wynalda, who was dropped by Steve Sampson for the 1998 World Cup?": {
        "original_answer": "John Harkes",
        "entities": [
            "Meola",
            "Wynalda"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was dropped by Steve Sampson for the 1998 World Cup?"
    },
    "Along with the Supreme Court, what political party did Fujimori disband in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Congress",
        "entities": [
            "the Supreme Court"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What political party did Fujimori disband in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, Estonia was forcibly incorporated into what in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "the Soviet Union",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania",
            "Estonia was forcibly incorporated into"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what did the Israelis capture in the 1967 Middle East war?": {
        "original_answer": "East Jerusalem",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did the Israelis capture in the 1967 Middle East war?"
    },
    "Along with Ambassador Jose Diaz Valdepares, who was freed on December 29, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "Ahmad Mokhtar",
        "entities": [
            "Ambassador Jose Diaz Valdepares"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was freed on December 29, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with the British, Sarazen won what other tournament in 1932?": {
        "original_answer": "U.S. Opens",
        "entities": [
            "the British",
            "Sarazen won"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other tournament in 1932?"
    },
    "Along with the Gulf of Mexico, what region has been under the jurisdiction of the Atlantic Command since 1950?": {
        "original_answer": "Caribbean",
        "entities": [
            "the Gulf of Mexico"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What region has been under the jurisdiction of the Atlantic Command since 1950?"
    },
    "Along with Manchuria, what country did Japan invade in 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Korea",
        "entities": [
            "Manchuria"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Japan invade in 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Laos, what country did Nixon expand the fighting into in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Cambodia",
        "entities": [
            "Laos"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Nixon expand the fighting into in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with the Ford Motor Company's Lincoln division, what American luxury car manufacturer dominated the American luxury market in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Cadillac",
        "entities": [
            "the Ford Motor Company's Lincoln division"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What American luxury car manufacturer dominated the American luxury market in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the West Bank, what did King Hussein lose in 1967?": {
        "original_answer": "East Jerusalem",
        "entities": [
            "the West Bank"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What did King Hussein lose in 1967?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Lithuania, what Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Latvia",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, Saudi Arabia and the Persian Gulf emirates, what Arab state joined the anti-Iraq alliance in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Syria",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "the Persian Gulf emirates"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab state joined the anti-Iraq alliance in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with SUNY, what other university did Cuomo propose steep cuts in 1992's budgets?": {
        "original_answer": "CUNY",
        "entities": [
            "SUNY"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other university did Cuomo propose steep cuts in 1992's budgets?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia and Lithuania, what other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia",
            "Lithuania"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Cuba, Angola and Namibia, what country signed a protocol in 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "South Africa",
        "entities": [
            "Cuba",
            "Angola",
            "Namibia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a protocol in 1988?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Muslims, what ethnic group fought in the Yugoslavian wars in the 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "Croats",
        "entities": [
            "Muslims"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group fought in the Yugoslavian wars in the 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Peng Zhen, who died in 1997 as Yang Shangkun?": {
        "original_answer": "Deng",
        "entities": [
            "Peng Zhen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who died in 1997 as Yang Shangkun?"
    },
    "Along with Shiite and Sunni leaders, what group abandoned negotiations with Sunnis on August 26, 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Kurdish",
        "entities": [
            "Shiite",
            "Sunni leaders"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What group abandoned negotiations with Sunnis on August 26, 2005?"
    },
    "Along with the Mars Climate Orbiter, what spacecraft failed in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "Mars Polar Lander",
        "entities": [
            "the Mars Climate Orbiter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What spacecraft failed in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Hyundai and Samsung, what company won 90 percent of the contracts for L.N.G. tankers awarded worldwide in 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Daewoo",
        "entities": [
            "Hyundai",
            "Samsung"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company won 90 percent of the contracts for L.N.G. tankers awarded worldwide in 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Killswitch Engage, what band of God has sold several hundred thousand records in 2005?": {
        "original_answer": "Lamb",
        "entities": [
            "Killswitch Engage"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What band of God has sold several hundred thousand records in 2005?"
    },
    "Along with Khieu Samphan, what Khmer Rouge leader defected in December, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Nuon Chea",
        "entities": [
            "Khieu Samphan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Khmer Rouge leader defected in December, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Latvia, what other Baltic republic lost its independence in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic lost its independence in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Diesel Jeans, what brand did Russ develop in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Von Furstenberg",
        "entities": [
            "Diesel Jeans"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What brand did Russ develop in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Maryland champions, what state filed protests on August 06, 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "New Jersey State",
        "entities": [
            "the Maryland champions"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state filed protests on August 06, 2002?"
    },
    "Along with other militia forces, what army sent 2,000 soldiers to the area on February 05, 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the Chinese Army",
        "entities": [
            "other militia forces"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What army sent 2,000 soldiers to the area on February 05, 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Britain, what country left the European monetary system in September, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Italy",
        "entities": [
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country left the European monetary system in September, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with China and Japan, what country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "South Korea",
        "entities": [
            "China",
            "Japan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Cheney visit in April, 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Burton, who held hearings on the siege in 1996?": {
        "original_answer": "the House Judiciary Committee",
        "entities": [
            "Burton"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who held hearings on the siege in 1996?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia and Slovenia, what country was recognized by the United States on April 07, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Bosnia and Herzegovina",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia",
            "Slovenia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was recognized by the United States on April 07, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the Soviets, what pact was used to suppress the Prague Spring in 1968?": {
        "original_answer": "Warsaw Pact",
        "entities": [
            "the Soviets"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What pact was used to suppress the Prague Spring in 1968?"
    },
    "Along with El Salvador, Honduras, Guatemala and Nicaragua, what country joined Nicaragua in the agreement announced on February 21, 1989?": {
        "original_answer": "Costa Rica",
        "entities": [
            "El Salvador",
            "Honduras",
            "Guatemala",
            "Nicaragua"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country joined Nicaragua in the agreement announced on February 21, 1989?"
    },
    "Along with Western Slavonia, what rebel Serb enclave was taken back by Croatian forces in 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Krajina",
        "entities": [
            "Western Slavonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What rebel Serb enclave was taken back by Croatian forces in 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Omarska, Keraterm and what other camp was closed in August 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Trnopolje",
        "entities": [
            "Omarska",
            "Keraterm"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other camp was closed in August 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Mark Pearlman, who was killed at the Sheraton Hotel in 1981?": {
        "original_answer": "Michael Hammer",
        "entities": [
            "Mark Pearlman"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was killed at the Sheraton Hotel in 1981?"
    },
    "Along with Kenya, what other country was blamed for the 1998 embassy bombings?": {
        "original_answer": "Tanzania",
        "entities": [
            "Kenya"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country was blamed for the 1998 embassy bombings?"
    },
    "Along with Sean Combs and Mr. Kors, what company is up for Men's Wear Designer of 2004?": {
        "original_answer": "Ralph Lauren",
        "entities": [
            "Sean Combs",
            "Mr. Kors"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company is up for Men's Wear Designer of 2004?"
    },
    "Along with Jammu and Kashmir, what district saw an Indian strike on October 16, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Poonch",
        "entities": [
            "Jammu",
            "Kashmir"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What district saw an Indian strike on October 16, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Sibelius, what composer will Leonard Bernstein conduct on August 15, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Mozart",
        "entities": [
            "Sibelius"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What composer will Leonard Bernstein conduct on August 15, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the French, what government agreed to a project in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "British",
        "entities": [
            "the French"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What government agreed to a project in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Nancy Kerrigan, who starred in the 1994 Winter Olympics?": {
        "original_answer": "Tonya Harding",
        "entities": [
            "Nancy Kerrigan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who starred in the 1994 Winter Olympics?"
    },
    "Along with Rivera, who collected information on two dozen police officers in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Vazquez",
        "entities": [
            "Rivera"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who collected information on two dozen police officers in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with the Port Authority of New York, what state lost 74 people in the 1993 trade center bombing?": {
        "original_answer": "New Jersey",
        "entities": [
            "the Port Authority of New York"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state lost 74 people in the 1993 trade center bombing?"
    },
    "Along with China, what country signed an accord to return Hong Kong to Chinese rule in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "Britain",
        "entities": [
            "China"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an accord to return Hong Kong to Chinese rule in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with the Screen Actors Guild, what other group is scheduled to strike on June 30, 2000?": {
        "original_answer": "the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists",
        "entities": [
            "the Screen Actors Guild"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other group is scheduled to strike on June 30, 2000?"
    },
    "Along with Musicland, who did Best Buy acquire in 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Sam Goody",
        "entities": [
            "Musicland"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Best Buy acquire in 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Lithuania, Latvia, and what other Baltic republic, what other republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Estonia",
        "entities": [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia,"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other Baltic republic, what other republic was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with the American Mariner, what mission orbited Mars in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Viking",
        "entities": [
            "the American Mariner"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What mission orbited Mars in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Hewlett-Packard, what company donated equipment to Earth Day 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Apple Computer",
        "entities": [
            "Hewlett-Packard"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company donated equipment to Earth Day 1990?"
    },
    "Along with American incursions, what country has invaded Cambodia since the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "Vietnamese",
        "entities": [
            "American incursions"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has invaded Cambodia since the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Sega, what company released the first 16-bit games in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Nintendo of America",
        "entities": [
            "Sega"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What company released the first 16-bit games in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with President Hussein, what other country's leaders met with Mr. Talabani in 1984?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraqi",
        "entities": [
            "President Hussein"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other country's leaders met with Mr. Talabani in 1984?"
    },
    "Along with Serbia and Bosnia, what country was a regional power before 1350?": {
        "original_answer": "Croatia",
        "entities": [
            "Serbia",
            "Bosnia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was a regional power before 1350?"
    },
    "Along with France and Britain, what country did Iran open negotiations with in 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "Germany",
        "entities": [
            "France",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country did Iran open negotiations with in 2003?"
    },
    "Along with Chase Manhattan, what bank closed branches in the neighborhood in 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Chemical Bank",
        "entities": [
            "Chase Manhattan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What bank closed branches in the neighborhood in 1987?"
    },
    "Along with a Jewish cultural center, what was struck in Argentina by Hezbollah in the early 1990's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Israeli Embassy",
        "entities": [
            "a Jewish cultural center"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What was struck in Argentina by Hezbollah in the early 1990's?"
    },
    "Along with Jordan, what country signed an agreement with the Palestinians on September 13, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Israel",
        "entities": [
            "Jordan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed an agreement with the Palestinians on September 13, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Gaza, what part of the country was closed off on December 13, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "the West Bank",
        "entities": [
            "Gaza"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What part of the country was closed off on December 13, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with the Pioneer and Challenger, what other spacecraft did Jupiter fly in the 1970's?": {
        "original_answer": "Voyager",
        "entities": [
            "the Pioneer",
            "Challenger"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other spacecraft did Jupiter fly in the 1970's?"
    },
    "Along with Eastern Airlines, what airline announced fare cuts on August 13, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Trans World Airlines",
        "entities": [
            "Eastern Airlines"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What airline announced fare cuts on August 13, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with the Port Authority of New York, what other state hired him in 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "New Jersey",
        "entities": [
            "the Port Authority of New York"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other state hired him in 1994?"
    },
    "Along with Tajikistan and Uzbekistan, what country will Baker visit on February 02, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Turkmenistan",
        "entities": [
            "Tajikistan",
            "Uzbekistan"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country will Baker visit on February 02, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Sirri, what oil platform was attacked by the U.S. on April 19, 1988?": {
        "original_answer": "Sassan",
        "entities": [
            "Sirri"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What oil platform was attacked by the U.S. on April 19, 1988?"
    },
    "Along with the Doors, what underground band did Pulnoc go back to in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Velvet Underground",
        "entities": [
            "the Doors"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What underground band did Pulnoc go back to in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Daschle, who was sent the letters to on October 09, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Leahy",
        "entities": [
            "Daschle"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was sent the letters to on October 09, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with Polish troops, who occupied Berlin in May 1945?": {
        "original_answer": "Russian",
        "entities": [
            "Polish troops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who occupied Berlin in May 1945?"
    },
    "Along with Egypt, Syria, and Lebanon, what Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?": {
        "original_answer": "Jordan",
        "entities": [
            "Egypt",
            "Syria",
            "and Lebanon"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Arab country declared war on May 15, 1948?"
    },
    "Along with Metallica, 2Pac, Pearl Jam and RZA, what band released a new album on November 24, 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "the Wu-Tang Clan's",
        "entities": [
            "Metallica",
            "2Pac",
            "Pearl Jam",
            "RZA"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What band released a new album on November 24, 1998?"
    },
    "Along with the New York Urban League, what organization did McCall serve on in the 1960's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Congress for Racial Equality",
        "entities": [
            "the New York Urban League"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What organization did McCall serve on in the 1960's?"
    },
    "Along with Georgia, Florida and what other state, at least 13 people died in floods by March, 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Alabama",
        "entities": [
            "Georgia",
            "Florida"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other state, at least 13 people died in floods by March, 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Anne-Sophie Mutter, who gave a series of Beethoven recitals in 1998?": {
        "original_answer": "Lambert Orkis",
        "entities": [
            "Anne-Sophie Mutter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who gave a series of Beethoven recitals in 1998?"
    },
    "Along with Abdel Basset Ali Megrahi, who was indicted in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Lamen Khalifa Fhimah",
        "entities": [
            "Abdel Basset Ali Megrahi"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was indicted in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Claude Berri and Isabelle Adjani, what director visited Balladur on October 19, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Roman Polanski",
        "entities": [
            "Claude Berri",
            "Isabelle Adjani"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What director visited Balladur on October 19, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with Racine and Kenosha, what Wisconsin city did he represent in 1970?": {
        "original_answer": "Janesville",
        "entities": [
            "Racine",
            "Kenosha"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Wisconsin city did he represent in 1970?"
    },
    "Along with the United States and Britain, what country resubmitted the Middle East resolution on May 12, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Russia",
        "entities": [
            "the United States",
            "Britain"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country resubmitted the Middle East resolution on May 12, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Mr. Teeter, who did Bush talk strategy with on July 13, 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Skinner",
        "entities": [
            "Mr. Teeter"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Bush talk strategy with on July 13, 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Morgan Stanley, what bank did Yukos approach for a $500 million loan in the summer of 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Chase Manhattan",
        "entities": [
            "Morgan Stanley"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What bank did Yukos approach for a $500 million loan in the summer of 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Isa Zainudinov, who was sentenced to life imprisonment on March 20, 2001?": {
        "original_answer": "Alisultan Salikhov",
        "entities": [
            "Isa Zainudinov"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was sentenced to life imprisonment on March 20, 2001?"
    },
    "Along with conservatives and timid freshmen, who were the 27 lawmakers who voted against the budget bill in March, 1993?": {
        "original_answer": "Texans",
        "entities": [
            "conservatives",
            "timid freshmen"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who were the 27 lawmakers who voted against the budget bill in March, 1993?"
    },
    "Along with the Plymouth Reliant, what Chrysler K-car was instrumental in the company's financial recovery in the early 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "the Dodge Aries",
        "entities": [
            "the Plymouth Reliant"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Chrysler K-car was instrumental in the company's financial recovery in the early 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with Court TV and local stations, what television station aired a murder case in Stamford in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "CBS",
        "entities": [
            "Court TV",
            "local stations"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What television station aired a murder case in Stamford in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with Iran, what country attacked Emirate oilfields in November, 1987?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraq",
        "entities": [
            "Iran"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country attacked Emirate oilfields in November, 1987?"
    },
    "Along with the Welsh National Assembly, what other assembly was created in 1999?": {
        "original_answer": "the Northern Ireland Assembly",
        "entities": [
            "the Welsh National Assembly"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other assembly was created in 1999?"
    },
    "Along with Steffi Graf, who was a top player at 1993's Open?": {
        "original_answer": "Stefan Edberg",
        "entities": [
            "Steffi Graf"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who was a top player at 1993's Open?"
    },
    "Along with Toyota, what other car manufacturer announced they were halting local production until 1997?": {
        "original_answer": "Isuzu",
        "entities": [
            "Toyota"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What other car manufacturer announced they were halting local production until 1997?"
    },
    "Along with Joan Collins, what Concorde stalwart flew free on October 24, 2003?": {
        "original_answer": "David Frost",
        "entities": [
            "Joan Collins"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Concorde stalwart flew free on October 24, 2003?"
    },
    "Along with California and Colorado, what state voted for term limits in 1990?": {
        "original_answer": "Oklahoma",
        "entities": [
            "California",
            "Colorado"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What state voted for term limits in 1990?"
    },
    "Along with Bosnians, what ethnic group seized eastern Bosnia in October, 1995?": {
        "original_answer": "Croat",
        "entities": [
            "Bosnians"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What ethnic group seized eastern Bosnia in October, 1995?"
    },
    "Along with Argentina, Brazil and Paraguay, what country signed a treaty in 1991?": {
        "original_answer": "Uruguay",
        "entities": [
            "Argentina",
            "Brazil",
            "Paraguay"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country signed a treaty in 1991?"
    },
    "Along with the Liberal Democrats, what center party dominated British politics in the early 1980's?": {
        "original_answer": "Social Democrats",
        "entities": [
            "the Liberal Democrats"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What center party dominated British politics in the early 1980's?"
    },
    "Along with CNBC and USA, what cable network broadcast more than 375 hours in Salt Lake City in 2002?": {
        "original_answer": "MSNBC",
        "entities": [
            "CNBC",
            "USA"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What cable network broadcast more than 375 hours in Salt Lake City in 2002?"
    },
    "Along with Croatia, what former republic gained independence in 1992?": {
        "original_answer": "Slovenia",
        "entities": [
            "Croatia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What former republic gained independence in 1992?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia, what country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with American troops, what country has sent troops to Baghdad in 2007?": {
        "original_answer": "Iraqi",
        "entities": [
            "American troops"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What country has sent troops to Baghdad in 2007?"
    },
    "Along with Estonia and Latvia, what Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?": {
        "original_answer": "Lithuania",
        "entities": [
            "Estonia",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "What Baltic state was annexed by the Soviet Union in 1940?"
    },
    "Along with Denis Irwin, who did Charlton have the services of on July 04, 1994?": {
        "original_answer": "Terry Phelan",
        "entities": [
            "Denis Irwin"
        ],
        "rephrased_question": "Who did Charlton have the services of on July 04, 1994?"
    }
}